<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:coveo="https://www.coveo.com/en/company/about-us">
    <url>
        <loc>https://www.usana.com/ux/cart/en-US/page/pc-signup</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-02-03</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Preferred Customer Sign Up</title>
            <body>The Perks of Becoming a Preferred CustomerCreate your free Preferred Customer account and gain access to exciting benefits specially designed to help you on your path to a healthier you. Sign me up Save 10%Easy Account ManagementSubscription OpportunitiesSave 10%Receive special Preferred Pricing on all USANA products. That&apos;s 10% off the retail price by simply creating an account.Easy Account ManagementYour Preferred Customer account makes it easy to track your order status and reorder the products you love. Plus, you will have access to a personal Independent Distributor who can help you get the health information you need to fuel your healthy goals.Subscription OpportunitiesAs a Preferred Customer, you can save even more by subscribing to your favorite products. By signing up for our Auto Order program, you can save an additional 10% off the Preferred Price and get your products delivered right to your door every month so you can easily keep up your healthy habits. Do Not Sell My Personal InformationWhen you visit our website, we store cookies on your browser to collect information. The information collected might relate to you, your preferences or your device, and is mostly used to make the site work as you expect it to and to provide a more personalized web experience. However, you can choose not to allow certain types of cookies, which may impact your experience of the site and the services we are able to offer. Click on the different category headings to find out more and change our default settings according to your preference. You cannot opt-out of our First Party Strictly Necessary Cookies as they are deployed in order to ensure the proper functioning of our website (such as prompting the cookie banner and remembering your settings, to log into your account, to redirect you when you log out, etc.). For more information about the First and Third Party Cookies used please follow this link. More informationAllow All Manage Consent PreferencesStrictly Necessary CookiesAlways ActiveThese cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information.Sale of Personal Data Sale of Personal Data Under the California Consumer Privacy Act, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information to third parties. These cookies collect information for analytics and to personalize your experience with targeted ads. You may exercise your right to opt out of the sale of personal information by using this toggle switch. If you opt out we will not be able to offer you personalised ads and will not hand over your personal information to any third parties. Additionally, you may contact our legal department for further clarification about your rights as a California consumer by using this Exercise My Rights link. If you have enabled privacy controls on your browser (such as a plugin), we have to take that as a valid request to opt-out. Therefore we would not be able to track your activity through the web. This may affect our ability to personalize ads according to your preferences.Performance Cookies Switch Label labelThese cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.Social Media Cookies Switch Label labelThese cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to the site to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit. If you do not allow these cookies you may not be able to use or see these sharing tools.Targeting Cookies Switch Label labelThese cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. They do not store directly personal information, but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.Back ButtonPerformance Cookies Clear checkbox label labelApply CancelConsent Leg.Interest checkbox label label checkbox label label checkbox label label Confirm My Choices</body>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>
    <url>
        <loc>https://www.usana.com/ux/cart/en-US/page/affiliate-signup</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-02-03</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Affiliate Sign Up</title>
            <body>Sign Up Amplify Your Influence as a USANA AffiliateOur niche is whole body health. Premium, science-backed nutritional supplements, foods for your active lifestyle, and targeted skincare for a brighter, glowier, hydrated complexion. We’re inspired by you. And we’ve made it simple to earn in your day to day. The Perks15% commission on salesRefer a friend to earn even more rewardsPreferred pricing on USANA productsEarn with Personalized LinksReceive 15% commission on every order placed through your personal link—with customers tied to you for life. Each future purchase adds up. Find your commission totals on the dashboard!Referral RewardsEarn more when you make new connections—and they earn, too! Refer an Affiliate to USANA to earn 10% on sales on any commissions they earn from their personal links. Referral rewards are in addition to regular commission earnings.Preferred PricingAffiliates enjoy preferred pricing when they join. Find your daily go-tos and save.How it WorksShare. Give followers a glimpse of your world.Earn. And track as you go.Repeat. This one’s all you.Share.Expand your influence with engaging social content or in-person connection—whatever’s distinctly you. Personal links make it easy to share. Create your every day, add your link, and bring us along!Earn.This is a community designed around you—let the true you shine, inspire others, and earn along the way. Access your user-friendly dashboard to check your stats (updated weekly!).Repeat.Create, innovate, and check in often for exciting tools and resources. Oh, and have fun!Let’s Do This!Join our community of healthy lifestyle enthusiasts—doers, movers, influencers, and innovators who share USANA their way. Sign Up Now Do Not Sell My Personal InformationWhen you visit our website, we store cookies on your browser to collect information. The information collected might relate to you, your preferences or your device, and is mostly used to make the site work as you expect it to and to provide a more personalized web experience. However, you can choose not to allow certain types of cookies, which may impact your experience of the site and the services we are able to offer. Click on the different category headings to find out more and change our default settings according to your preference. You cannot opt-out of our First Party Strictly Necessary Cookies as they are deployed in order to ensure the proper functioning of our website (such as prompting the cookie banner and remembering your settings, to log into your account, to redirect you when you log out, etc.). For more information about the First and Third Party Cookies used please follow this link. More informationAllow All Manage Consent PreferencesStrictly Necessary CookiesAlways ActiveThese cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information.Sale of Personal Data Sale of Personal Data Under the California Consumer Privacy Act, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information to third parties. These cookies collect information for analytics and to personalize your experience with targeted ads. You may exercise your right to opt out of the sale of personal information by using this toggle switch. If you opt out we will not be able to offer you personalised ads and will not hand over your personal information to any third parties. Additionally, you may contact our legal department for further clarification about your rights as a California consumer by using this Exercise My Rights link. If you have enabled privacy controls on your browser (such as a plugin), we have to take that as a valid request to opt-out. Therefore we would not be able to track your activity through the web. This may affect our ability to personalize ads according to your preferences.Performance Cookies Switch Label labelThese cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.Social Media Cookies Switch Label labelThese cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to the site to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit. If you do not allow these cookies you may not be able to use or see these sharing tools.Targeting Cookies Switch Label labelThese cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. They do not store directly personal information, but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.Back ButtonPerformance Cookies Clear checkbox label labelApply CancelConsent Leg.Interest checkbox label label checkbox label label checkbox label label Confirm My Choices</body>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>
    <url>
        <loc>https://www.usana.com/ux/dotcom/enu-US/opportunity</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-02-03</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Business Opportunity</title>
            <body>Invest in Yourself Grow your income while investing in your health, skills, and personal growth. Turn Your Passion into Income Start SharingShare your favorite products to earn. Small actions build momentum.Start EarningEarn flexible income on your terms. Create long-term potential that grows with you.Start GrowingDevelop your skills. Tap into a community that supports your goals. Let’s Grow Together Develop valuable skills in leadership, wellness, and business through expert-led trainings and partnerships with world-class institutes. All while being mentored by a community that champions your success. Thousands of Lives Changed “With USANA, I’ve improved my lifestyle while creating a business I love.”-Adryleen A.Brand Partner“USANA gives me the flexibility to work when I want and enjoy my family.”-Grace N.Brand Partner“USANA helped me find community, mentorship, and purpose.”-Ashley M. Brand Partner Your Path to a Purpose-Driven Lifestyle With travel opportunities, rewards that match your efforts, and a flexible work-life balance, this is your chance to unlock your potential and live with purpose. Premium Products World-class, science backed Competitive Compensation Early income potential Scalable Earnings Sustainable growth Personal Mentorship Develop your skills Low-risk Minimal cost, easy onboarding Easy Management No inventory, no shipping Start Small, Dream Big Not feeling ready to become a Brand Partner? Explore other ways to get involved with USANA. Affiliate Share your favorite products with followers and get credit when they buy. Learn More Preferred Customer Enjoy exclusive discounts on your favorite products. Learn More Answers to Get You StartedWhat is a USANA Brand Partner? When you enroll as a Brand Partner, you can sell world-class products, get paid weekly commissions, earn extra bonuses, and be eligible to win additional rewards like luxury travel and recognition. You can become more than a social media influencer or product distributor—you’ll be part of a global health-focused community driven by a shared vision to make a positive difference in the world. How much can I earn as a Brand Partner? Your earnings match your efforts, and commission payouts occur weekly so you’ll quickly see the impact of your hard work. Whether you want to add to your current income or build a new path, this opportunity is flexible, scalable, and designed to grow with you. Tell me more about the expert-led wellness trainings USANA offers. We’ve partnered with a world-class holistic health and wellness institute—Sanoviv—to provide an expert-led certification course exclusive to USANA Brand Partners. You can learn about emerging nutrition-focused wellness and lifestyle topics through a 10-course program taught by Sanoviv’s medical experts and nutritionists. After you’ve completed the program, you’ll be a certified nutritional advisor ready to help others achieve their wellness goals and make the world a healthier place. How do I get started? Getting started is easy—enroll as a Brand Partner and begin sharing your favorite products to start earning. Once you enroll, we’ll walk you through a simple step-by-step onboarding experience and teach you how to earn your first paycheck. USANA offers bonuses to beginners so you can receive day-one earnings. What is the time and money investment of becoming a Brand Partner? You don’t need a big investment to start, and you don’t have to quit your job or change your routine. You work anywhere, anytime. Whether it’s during your lunch break, weekends, or while traveling, you’re in control of your schedule. A low startup cost makes it easy for you to take this first step to something better. And USANA fits alongside your current commitments, adding value without disruption. Do I already need business experience to succeed? Not at all, you just need the drive to succeed! The key to being a Brand Partner is sharing your unique health story and being your authentic self. We’ll provide you with easy-to-use digital tools and trainings to begin selling and earning right away. When you’re ready, you can leverage more of our online resources to help you grow a team and maximize your income. What sustainability and/or community outreach efforts is USANA involved with? USANA was founded with a mission to create the healthiest family on earth, and you can be part of this mission. Our USANA Foundation collaborates with Brand Partners to fight malnutrition worldwide. Since 2012, we’ve served more than 45 countries and provided more than 112 million meals to those in need. And our commitment to sustainability extends far beyond simply doing good—it is intricately woven into our strategy for long-term success. How long has USANA operated and how many countries do you operate in? USANA offers transparency, stability, and a legacy you can trust. We’re publicly traded on the NYSE and we’ve been developing state-of-the-art health and wellness products for over 30 years. We operate globally in 25 international markets, giving you the opportunity to grow a business with a well-known brand. We’ve paid out over $2.2 billion to Brand Partners in the past five years, a solid track record of reliability and reward. Be More with USANA: The Cellular Nutrition Company. Are you ready to get obsessed with the health of your cells and feel the difference optimal cellular nutrition can make in your life? You&apos;re in the right place! To get started, please verify your country and preferred language. United States - English United States English Español 繁體中文 簡體中文 Canada English Français 繁體中文 簡體中文 Mexico Español Colombia Español Netherlands English United Kingdom English France Français English Belgium Français English Germany English Deutsch Spain English Español Italy English Italiano Romania English Română Hong Kong English 繁體中文 Japan 日本語 Korea 한국어 Taiwan 繁體中文 Australia English 簡體中文 New Zealand English 簡體中文 India English Indonesia English Indonesian Malaysia English Malay 簡體中文 Singapore English 简体中文 Thailand ภาษาไทย Philippines English OK

--- Frequently Asked Questions ---

Q: What is a USANA Brand Partner?
A: When you enroll as a Brand Partner, you can sell world-class products, get paid weekly commissions, earn extra bonuses, and be eligible to win additional rewards like luxury travel and recognition. You can become more than a social media influencer or product distributor—you’ll be part of a global health-focused community driven by a shared vision to make a positive difference in the world.

Q: How much can I earn as a Brand Partner?
A: Your earnings match your efforts, and commission payouts occur weekly so you’ll quickly see the impact of your hard work. Whether you want to add to your current income or build a new path, this opportunity is flexible, scalable, and designed to grow with you.

Q: Tell me more about the expert-led wellness trainings USANA offers.
A: We’ve partnered with a world-class holistic health and wellness institute—Sanoviv—to provide an expert-led certification course exclusive to USANA Brand Partners. You can learn about emerging nutrition-focused wellness and lifestyle topics through a 10-course program taught by Sanoviv’s medical experts and nutritionists. After you’ve completed the program, you’ll be a certified nutritional advisor ready to help others achieve their wellness goals and make the world a healthier place.

Q: How do I get started?
A: Getting started is easy—enroll as a Brand Partner and begin sharing your favorite products to start earning. Once you enroll, we’ll walk you through a simple step-by-step onboarding experience and teach you how to earn your first paycheck. USANA offers bonuses to beginners so you can receive day-one earnings.

Q: What is the time and money investment of becoming a Brand Partner?
A: You don’t need a big investment to start, and you don’t have to quit your job or change your routine. You work anywhere, anytime. Whether it’s during your lunch break, weekends, or while traveling, you’re in control of your schedule. A low startup cost makes it easy for you to take this first step to something better. And USANA fits alongside your current commitments, adding value without disruption.

Q: Do I already need business experience to succeed?
A: Not at all, you just need the drive to succeed! The key to being a Brand Partner is sharing your unique health story and being your authentic self. We’ll provide you with easy-to-use digital tools and trainings to begin selling and earning right away. When you’re ready, you can leverage more of our online resources to help you grow a team and maximize your income.

Q: What sustainability and/or community outreach efforts is USANA involved with?
A: USANA was founded with a mission to create the healthiest family on earth, and you can be part of this mission. Our USANA Foundation collaborates with Brand Partners to fight malnutrition worldwide. Since 2012, we’ve served more than 45 countries and provided more than 112 million meals to those in need. And our commitment to sustainability extends far beyond simply doing good—it is intricately woven into our strategy for long-term success.

Q: How long has USANA operated and how many countries do you operate in?
A: USANA offers transparency, stability, and a legacy you can trust. We’re publicly traded on the NYSE and we’ve been developing state-of-the-art health and wellness products for over 30 years. We operate globally in 25 international markets, giving you the opportunity to grow a business with a well-known brand. We’ve paid out over $2.2 billion to Brand Partners in the past five years, a solid track record of reliability and reward.</body>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>
    <url>
        <loc>https://www.usana.com/ux/dotcom/enu-US/refund-and-return-policy</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-02-03</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Refund and Return Policy</title>
            <body>PRODUCT REFUND AND RETURN POLICYProduct Exchange USANA warrants the quality of its products and shall exchange any defective product. Anyone returning a damaged or defective product must complete the Associate Product Exchange or Return. Product exchanges made for the purpose of favorable gain through maximizing commissions or manipulating the Binary Compensation Plan (as evidenced through patterns observed outside of the average Associate pattern of exchanges) will not be honored and are considered a material breach of the Associate Agreement.THIRTY (30) DAY RETURN POLICY Retail Customers USANA obligates its Associates to honor the Company’s 100 percent, unconditional, 30-day, money-back guarantee to all retail customers. If for any reason a retail customer is dissatisfied with any USANA product, he/she may return the product to the Associate from whom the product was purchased within thirty (30) days from the date of purchase for a replacement, exchange, or full refund of the purchase price. If the retail customer requests a refund, the Associate who sold the product to the retail customer must immediately refund the retail customer’s purchase price. (Retail customers must return merchandise to the Associate who sold it to them; USANA will not accept returned merchandise directly from retail customers.) The Associate, in turn, should complete a Dissatisfied Consumer Product Return and forward the form along with the original sales receipt and returned merchandise to USANA. USANA will then replace the returned merchandise with like product and ship it to the Associate. All retail customers must be provided with two copies of an official USANA Retail Sales Receipt at the time of the sale. The back of the receipt provides the customer with written notice of his/her rights to cancel the sales agreement. Preferred Customers USANA offers Preferred Customers, and retail customers who order directly from an official USANA Web site, a 100 percent, 30-day, money back guarantee on their initial product order. If for any reason a Preferred Customer is dissatisfied with any USANA product, he/she may return that product to the Company within thirty (30) days for replacement, exchange, or full refund of the purchase price. If a Preferred Customer returns merchandise equal to or exceeding $100.00 US, this will be deemed a Voluntary Cancellation. For all other returns, the Company shall repurchase the inventory pursuant to the terms of section 7.3. Moreover, the Company will adjust the appropriate Associates’ sales volume pursuant to section 6.2. Be More with USANA: The Cellular Nutrition Company. Are you ready to get obsessed with the health of your cells and feel the difference optimal cellular nutrition can make in your life? You&apos;re in the right place! To get started, please verify your country and preferred language. United States - English United States English Español 繁體中文 簡體中文 Canada English Français 繁體中文 簡體中文 Mexico Español Colombia Español Netherlands English United Kingdom English France Français English Belgium Français English Germany English Deutsch Spain English Español Italy English Italiano Romania English Română Hong Kong English 繁體中文 Japan 日本語 Korea 한국어 Taiwan 繁體中文 Australia English 簡體中文 New Zealand English 簡體中文 India English Indonesia English Indonesian Malaysia English Malay 簡體中文 Singapore English 简体中文 Thailand ภาษาไทย Philippines English OK</body>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>
    <url>
        <loc>https://www.usana.com/ux/dotcom/enu-US/give-back/thf</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-02-03</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Give Back - USANA True Health Foundation</title>
            <body>Donate NowThe USANA Foundation’s mission is to develop a network of communities built on long-lasting, sustainable, and nutritious food. The USANA Foundation provides immediate and long-term global food relief for those in severe need. We lead a network of community-driven partnerships to nourish, equip, and eliminate hunger throughout the world. When you donate to us, you&apos;re helping those who need it most.Donate Monthly donations provide the USANA Foundation a steady source of funding that continually supports our expansive network of partners and hundreds of global Garden Tower communities. ServeGlobal and local service trips are open to volunteers. Each trip focuses on strengthening our Garden Tower network by connecting with communities and establishing new, sustainable food systems.SponsorEmpower a community and provide them with the resources needed to thrive. Sponsorships give donors a unique opportunity to connect with food-insecure communities both locally and globally.Because USANA covers our costs, every donation to the USANA Foundation goes directly into our nutrition-providing programs. Thanks for your support!DONATE NOW Be More with USANA: The Cellular Nutrition Company. Are you ready to get obsessed with the health of your cells and feel the difference optimal cellular nutrition can make in your life? You&apos;re in the right place! To get started, please verify your country and preferred language. United States - English United States English Español 繁體中文 簡體中文 Canada English Français 繁體中文 簡體中文 Mexico Español Colombia Español Netherlands English United Kingdom English France Français English Belgium Français English Germany English Deutsch Spain English Español Italy English Italiano Romania English Română Hong Kong English 繁體中文 Japan 日本語 Korea 한국어 Taiwan 繁體中文 Australia English 簡體中文 New Zealand English 簡體中文 India English Indonesia English Indonesian Malaysia English Malay 簡體中文 Singapore English 简体中文 Thailand ภาษาไทย Philippines English OK</body>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>
</urlset>
