<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset
    xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9"
    xmlns:coveo="https://www.coveo.com/en/company/about-us">

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/16</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Egg Drop Soup</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/c0a238747d4b41b4b1b40c2864c1e21c.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Chicken stock 4 cups; Salt 3/4 tsp; Green onions 1 bunch; White Pepper 1/8 tsp; Eggs 3 pieces; Turmeric 1/2 tsp; Monosodium Glutamate (MSG) 1/4 tsp; Sugar 1/8 tsp; Cornstarch 3 tbsp; Sesame oil 1/2 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Bring the chicken stock to a simmer in a medium pot then stir in the sesame oil, salt, sugar, white pepper, turmeric and MSG (if using). Taste the soup, and adjust the seasoning to your taste. | Next add the cornstarch and water mixture. Stir the soup continuously as you drizzle in the cornstarch slurry to make sure there are no clumps. | Use a spoon to stir the soup and slowly drizzle in all of the beaten eggs until until ribbons form. | Pour the soup into bowls and garnish with green onions, then serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>241</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/17</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Filipino Arroz Caldo</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/1cf6027027424169ab62b30985663805.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Boneless Chicken  1 1/2 lbs; Vegetable oil  2 tbsp; Fish sauce 2 tbsp; White rice 1 1/2 cups; Garlic 1 tsp; Black Pepper 1/4 tsp; Onion 1 cup; Lemon  1 piece; Green onion 1 bunch; Ginger 2 tbsp; Chicken bouillon 1 cube; Safflower or Turmeric 3 tbsp; Water 1 liter; Hard Boiled Egg 4 eggs</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a soup pot, heat the oil then saute the garlic, onion, and ginger until softened. | Next, add in ground black pepper to taste and chicken bouillon cube then cook until the chicken bouillon cube dissolves. | Add the boneless chicken pieces and cook until browned. | Add the fish sauce and uncooked rice then mix well. | Add the water in, making sure everything is covered, and bring to a low boil. Stir occasionally and simmer until the rice is fully cooked. (approximately 20-30 minutes) | Stir in the safflower or turmeric for additional color and flavor. | Garnish with sliced hard boiled eggs, fried garlic, green onions, and lemon, then serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>74</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/18</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Tom Kha Soup</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/5f1d1c33947947eaab71c0d7524255de.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>35</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Shrimp 10 ounces; Water 3 cups; Chicken Stock 1/2 cup; Lemongrass 2 stalks; Galangal 1.5 cm; Kaffir lime leaves 5 pieces; Red Thai chili 2 pieces; Garlic 3 cloves; Oyster mushrooms 4 ounces; Roma tomato 1 piece; White onion 1/2 piece; Sugar 1 tsp; Fish sauce 3 tbsp; Lime 3 tbsp; Cilantro 1 tsp; Coconut milk 1 can</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Using a mortar and pestle, or similar, bash the garlic, chilli and lemongrass so they burst open to release flavour then add into a soup pot. | Add the kaffir lime leaves, galangal, chicken stock and water to the pot. Simmer on high heat, cover, then reduce to medium heat and simmer for 10 minutes. | Strain the broth, discard the aromatics, then return broth into same pot over low heat. | Add onions, mushrooms, tomatoes, shrimp and simmer 2 minutes or until just cooked. Next stir in sugar, fish sauce, lime juice, and coconut milk. Adjust the seasonings to your liking. | Ladle into bowls and serve with fresh cilantro and more Thai chili!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>105</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/19</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Tofu with Century Egg and Pork Floss</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/4bd77b524a354a7fa3a0ea979473bf98.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Century eggs 3 pieces; Soft tofu 300 grams; Peanuts 30 grams; Pork floss 10 grams; Cilantro 1 bunch; Garlic 3 cloves; Green onions 1 bunch; Vegetable oil 2 tsp; Preserved vegetables 30 grams; Light soy sauce 2 tsp; Oyster sauce 2 tsp; Sugar 1 tsp; Water 60 ml; Cornstarch 1 1/2 tsp; Sesame oil 1 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a sauce pan on medium heat, add oil and add the garlic and white parts of green onions. Cook until garlic is golden then remove it from the pan and set aside. | Combine light soy sauce, oyster sauce, sugar, cornstarch and 60 ml water. | Using the same pan, add the chopped preserved vegetables and stir fry for 1 minute then pour in soy sauce mixture. Cook until sauce has thickened and add 1 tsp sesame oil. | Place the tofu on a serving plate and arrange the century eggs, pork floss, and peanuts on top of the tofu. Drizzle the sauce and garnish with green onions and cilantro.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>52</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/20</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Taiwanese Sesame Oil Chicken Soup</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/98e39a63739e4ef7a6c35716ceabf84b.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>45</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Chicken Legs 3 pounds; Black sesame oil 3 tbsp; Ginger 3 ounces; Michiu (Taiwanese rice wine) 750 ml; Rock sugar 20 grams; Salt 1 tsp; Green onions 2-3 stalks</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat your wok or skillet over medium heat, then add the black sesame oil along with the sliced ginger and cook for 2 minutes. | Turn up the heat to high, and sear the chicken legs (in batches if needed) until browned on all sides. Once the chicken legs are nicely browned, turn the heat back down to medium and add in rice wine, rock sugar, and water. | Cover and simmer over medium heat for 30 minutes. The soup should be bubbling, but not boiling. | The soup is ready once the chicken legs are tender. Season with salt to taste and garnish with scallions when serving.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>67</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/23</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Taro Coconut Sago</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/480b8966d1d5455898b416ec3050f8ca.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Sago Pearls 3/4 cup; Coconut Milk 1 1/2 cup; Sugar 1/3 cup; Whole milk 1 1/2 cup; Taro root 1 1/4 cup; Grass jelly 1/2 can; Yam and taro balls 1 cup</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a pot over medium heat, combine coconut milk, milk, and sugar. | Bring mixture to a boil and remove from heat. Set side. | Peel taro root then cut into slices and using a cookie cutter press out shapes. (Or dice into small 1/2-inch cubes) Steam until tender and a fork or toothpick pricks through, about 10 – 15 minutes and set aside. | In a small pot, cook sago pearls according to instructions on the package then set aside. | Dice grass jelly into small cubes. | Add all the prepared toppings to the coconut milk base. Stir to combine and enjoy! (Can be served hot or cold; chill for 2-4 hours if serving cold)</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>154</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/24</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Thai Basil Pork Stir Fry (Pad Kra Pao)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/613b2577fff848b982e525fa418573af.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>25</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Fish sauce 1 tbsp; Light soy sauce 1 tbsp; Kecap manis (Indonesian soy sauce)1 tbsp; Garlic 4 cloves; Oyster sauce 1 tbsp; Water 4 tbsp; Green beans 5.5 ounces; Minced pork 7 ounces; Basil 1/2 bunch; Red Thai Chili 3 pieces; Eggs 1-2 pieces</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Mix together the fish sauce, soy sauce, kecap manis, oyster sauce and water in a bowl or jug and set aside. | Heat up a large drizzle of oil in a wok or stir-fry pan. Then stir-fry the green beans for a few minutes on a medium high heat. Add the chopped chilis and garlic and stir-fry for a couple more minutes. | Add the pork and break up with a wooden spoon. Stir-fry until cooked (an additional few minutes). | Pour in the sauce, stir well, then let bubble for a minute or two more. | Stir in the basil until wilted, then serve with the rice and a fried egg.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>200</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/30</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Beef Chow Fun</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/69f3acc41d55483aba42d67a468c04ba.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>85</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Flank Steak 8 ounces; Baking Soda 1/4 tsp; Ginger 1 piece; Cornstarch 1 tsp; Shaoxing wine 2 tbsp; Green Onions 4 stalks; Wide Rice Noodles 12 ounces; Dark Soy Sauce 2 tsp; Vegetable Oil 1 tsp + 3 tsp; Bean Sprouts 5 ounces; Light Soy Sauce 1 tsp + 2 tbsp; Sugar 1/8 tsp; Sesame Oil 1/2 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a medium bowl mix together the flank steak, baking soda, cornstarch, vegetable oil, and soy sauce then marinate for 1 hour. | Heat up vegetable oil in a large skillet then cook the marinated beef until it has browned and remove from the pan. | Using the same pan add in ginger, green onions, wide rice noodles, Shaoxing wine, sesame oil, dark soy sauce, light soy sauce, cooked beef, sugar, and bean sprouts.  Mix well until everything is incorporated. | Add salt and white pepper to taste. | Serve and garnish with more green onions.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>153</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/31</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Sliced Pork with Garlic Sauce</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/330722ea21f44addbb3dd0c2ebedce22.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>105</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Pork Belly 1 pound; Water 6 cups; Ginger 5 slices; Star anise 1 piece; Shaoxing wine 2 tbsp; Green Onions 3 stalks; Sichuan peppercorns 2 tsp; Red Chili Flakes 2 tbsp; Vegetable Oil ⅓ cup; Garlic 10 cloves; Light Soy Sauce 3½ tbsp; Black Vinegar 1 tbsp; Sugar 1 tbsp; Sesame Oil 1 tsp; Sesame Paste 1 tbsp; Cucumber 1 piece; Toasted Sesame Seeds 1 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a large pot add the water, pork belly, ginger, star anise, Shaoxing wine, Sichuan peppercorns, and green onions then boil. | When the pork belly has cooked remove it from the pot and reserve 2 cups of the cooking liquid. | Slice the cooked pork belly. | Using a small bowl add in the minced garlic, ginger, green onions, chili flakes, sichuan peppercorns, boiling oil, soy sauce, black vinegar, sugar, sesame oil, sesame paste, reserved cooking liquid, and toasted sesame seeds then mix. | Place the cucumber slices in a large bowl then layer the slices of pork on top. | Pour the sauce over the pork and cucumbers, then garnish with green onions.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>72</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/32</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Braised Pork Belly</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/12f41afc693a4f0cbd2cfe10958137eb.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>100</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Pork Belly  2 lbs; Green Onion 1 bunch; Ginger  Few Slices; Mogami Canola Olive Oil 2 Tbsp; Simbo Yellow Rock Sugar 1 Tbsp; Asian Taste Shaoxing Cooking Wine  3 Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Soy Sauce 1 Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Premium Dark Soy Sauce 1/2 Tbsp; Water 2 cups</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cut pork belly into desired size. Bring water to boil and add in few slices of ginger, few stems of green onion, and pork belly. Cook the pork belly until it turn white on the surface  and take it out of the pot. | In a wok, with medium high heat, add in Vegeable Oil, Rock Sugar, and Pork Belly. Cook Until the pork belly turn brown. | Add in Shaoxing Wine, Soy Sauce and Dark Soy Sauce and cook for a few minutes | Add in Water, with medium low heat, cover with lid and simmer for 1 hour. Until most liquids are evaporated. | Ready to serve in your favorite dinnerware, and sprinkle some chopped Green Onion as garnish.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>563</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/33</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Hot &amp; Sour Napa Cabbage</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/4134427849224811a13d27c3ab5a2453.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Napa Cabbage 1 piece; Salt 1 tsp; Red Chili Flakes 1 tsp; Soy Sauce 2 tsp; Oyster Sauce 1 tsp; Red Thai Chili 4-6 pieces; Garlic 3 cloves; Green Onions 2 stalks; Vegetable Oil 3 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Remove napa cabbage root, split in half &amp;amp; cut into equal parts. | Rinse with water, add salt, and mix. | Let it sit for 20 minutes &amp;amp; drain water out. | Add in the red chili flakes, soy sauce, oyster sauce, Thai chilis, garlic, green onions, and boiling oil then mix to combine.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>56</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/34</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chicken Teriyaki</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/a208ff4dbd2245e4b3b81f546af6afa3.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>60</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Boneless Chicken Thigh  4 pcs; Onion 1/4 pcs; Ginger Desire Amount; Honbiou Cooking Wine 1 Tbsp; Wan Ja Shan Mirin 1 Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Soy Sauce 2 Tbsp; C&amp;amp;H Sugar 1 Tbsp; Water 2 Tbsp; Salt Desire Amount; Pepper Desire Amount</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a bowl, mix in ginger, onion, cooking wine, mirin, soy sauce, sugar, and water. | Use a fork to poke through the chicken thign. Season with salt &amp;amp; pepper on both sides and place inside the bowl of marinate. | In a pan, add oil with medium high heat, please the chicken thigh with the skin side down first. Flip to the otherside and repeat until the chicken is cooked. | Remove the chicken to the side. Clean out the pan residue. And place the chicke thigh back in the pan, pour in the remaining marinate, cook with medium heat until all the marinate evaoprates | Ready to serve. Eat alone or serve over rice and vegeatble as a complete meal</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>237</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/35</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Ginger Soy Fish</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/c3b2383f95194f79a456d48d78e1fbc7.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>White fish 12 ounces; Soy sauce 2 tbsp; Green Onions 1 piece; Sugar 1 tbsp; Sesame oil 1 tsp; Cornstarch 1 tbsp; Vegetable Oil 2 tbsp; White Pepper 1 tsp; Water 2 tbsp; Ginger 1 piece</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cut the white fish into cubes and coat evenly in cornstarch, then set aside. | Using a different bowl add in soy sauce, sesame oil, water, sugar, and white pepper then mix well with a whisk. | In a medium pan heat up the vegestable oil with the ginger slices until it has browned and set aside. | Fry the fish in the oil that was used to brown the ginger until each piece is crispy. | When the fish has browned add in the soy sauce mixture and stir to coat. | Remove the fish from the heat then serve with green onions and the crispy ginger.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>99</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/38</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Beijing Beef</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/4e3d45c1a9a545859ae06ddce79aa589.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>50</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Beef Flank Steak 1 lbs; Red Bell Pepper 1 pcs; Green Bell Pepper  1 pcs; Onion  1 pcs; Garlic  To desire amount; Egg Whites 3 pcs; Salt  1/4 tsp; Flying Horse Tapioca Starch  3 Tbsp; Water 1/2 cup; C&amp;amp;H Sugar 1/4 cup; Heinz Ketchup 3 Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Hoisin Sauce  6 Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Oyster Sauce 2 Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Thai Chili Sauce 4 tsp; Simbo Crushed Red Pepper 1 tsp; Kong Yen Rice Vinegar 2 Tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Slice beef to desired thickness. Mix with egg whites and tapioca powder, set it aside for 30 minutes for beef to tenderize | In another bowl, mix in water, sugar, ketchup, hoisin sauce, oyster sauce, thai chili sauce, crushed red pepper and rice vinegar | Coat the beef slices with taipioca powder, and deep fry it with medium high heet until golden brown and set it aside. | Discard the extra oil and only leave proper amount of oil in the pan, add in green bell pepper, red bell pepper, onion and garlic. Stir fy it until onion becomes translucent | In the same pan, add in the condiment mixture and bring to boil, add in the vegetable mix and beef, mix property and ready to serve.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>267</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/39</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Vegetarian Egg Roll</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/1a146709435e47ca81ad1546ff4ff780.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Wei - Chuan Egg Roll Shells 1 pack; Garlic  3 Tbsp; Asian Taste Dry Mushroom 3 Tbsp; Celery 4 oz; Cabbage 8 oz; Carrot 3 oz; Green Onion 3 oz; Cloud Ear Fungus Mushroom 3 oz; Salt 1 tsp; Lee Kum Kee White Pepper Powder 1 tsp; Lee Kum Kee Vegetarian Oyster Sauce 1 tsp; Sinbo Fine Rice Vermicelli  2 oz; Mizuho 100% Pure Sesame Oil 1 Tbsp; Gold Medal Flour  2 Tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a pan with medium high heat, add in oil, garlic, shitake mushroom, celebry, cabbage, carrot, green onion, cloud ear fungus mushroom, salt, sugar, vegetarian oyster sauce, vermicelli noodles, and sesame oil. Stir fry untl the ingredients become soft and set it aside | Take a egg roll wrapper, place proper amount of the vegetable mixture as the filling, roll upwards, fold the two sides and seal the wrapper with 1:1 water/ flour mixture | In a pan with medium high heat and oil, deep fry 2-3 minutes for each side | Egg rolls are now ready to serve. Be carefull of the hot filling!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>152</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/40</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Bo Kho</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/6485fa1f2c7e4caeb6bb6b78dadd9ac8.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>150</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Three Crabs Fish Sauce 2 Tbsp; Kimbo Brown Sugar 1 Tbsp; Ginger 4 Tbsp; Wu Hsing Five Spice Powder 2 Tbsp; Pepper 1/2 tsp; Beef Chuck 3 lbs; Red Onion 1; Garlic 2 Cloves; Lemongrass 3 Tbsp; Tomato  1; Salt 1 tsp; Tumeric Powder 1/2 Tsp; Water 4 cups; Cinnamon Stick 1; Red Thai Chilies Few; Carrots 1.5 lbs</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a bowl, mix fish sauce, brown sugar, ginger, Chinese 5 spice, and black pepper | In a large bowl, place beef chuck in desire size and mix in the seasoning mix from step 1. Cover the bowl and let it marinate for minimum 30 mins | In a pan, add some vegetable oil, and cookl the beef chuck in batches until all sides are seared, and set the beef aside | In the same pan, add in garlic, lemon grass, tomatic, salt, tumeric powderr, water, cinnamon stick, red Thai chilies. Place the beef back back in the pot. Bring to boil, turn down to medium low heat, cover the pot and simmer for 1 hour | Add in carrots and simmer for 15 minutes | Before serving, remove the cinnamon stick fromt the pot. Serve alone or with baguette/ rice</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>162</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/41</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Braised Eggplant with Garlic Sauce</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/04235f3261af43198e1de96e4b561d90.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>40</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Chinese Eggplant 2; Flying Horse Tapioca Starch  3 Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Soy Sauce 2 tsp; Asian Taste Chinkiang Vinegar 1 Tbsp; Water 1/2 Cup; C&amp;amp;H Sugar 2 Tbsp; Salt 1/4 Tsp; Ground Pork 1/4 lb; Lee Kum Kee Chili Bean Sauce 1 Tbsp; Garlic 3 Cloves; Ginger 2 Tbsp; LGM Pickled Chili 1 Tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Chop the eggplant to desired size. Coated with corn starch and set aside | Mix soy sauce, black vinegar, water, sugar, salt and corn starch together to make the sauce mixture | In a skillet, with medium high heat and vegetable oil, pan fry the eggplant until it&amp;#x27;s golden brown on both sides. Take the eggplant out and set it aside | In the same skillet, add in ground pork, chili bean paste, garlic, ginger and pickled pepper, stir fry until the pork is all the way cooked | Pour in the sauce mixture, add in the eggplant and mix until the sauce is evenly coated on the eggplant | Ready to serve. Optional, sprinkle some chopped green onion as garnish</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>230</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/42</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Honey Walnut Shrimp</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/2baea8970ddd4437a75edfd90c463160.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Blue Diamond Shrimp 1 lb; Water  1/2 Cup; C&amp;amp;H Sugar 1/2 Cup; Walnut Halves 1/2 Cup; Honey  1 1/2 tsp; Kewpie Mayo 3 Tbsp; Carnation Condensed Milk 1 1/2 tsp; Salt Proper Amount; Pepper Proper Amount; Egg 1; Flying Horse Tapioca Starch  1/2 cup</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a skillet, add in equal parts of water and sugar with medium low heat. Stir until the sugar is fully dissolved and add in the walnut halves. Evenly coat the syrup mix around the walnut halves, and set it aside | In a small bowl, mix honey, mayoonaise, condense milk together to make the glaze mixture | In a bowl, mix peeled and deveined shrimp, mix with salt, pepper and egg. Coat the each shrimp evenly with corn starch | In a skillet with medium high heat, fry the shrimp until it&amp;#x27;s golden brown and set it aside | In a bowl, mix the shrimp, glaze mixture, and evently coat the shrimp with the glaze mixture. Add in candied walnut, and it&amp;#x27;s ready to eat!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>341</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/43</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Kung Pao Chicken</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/3049d64a42b04b4dbbb557a1e7540216.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Chicken 2 lbs; Asian Taste Shaoxing Cooking Wine  3 Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Soy Sauce 6 Tbsp; Baking Soda 1 1/2 tsp; Kimbow Chicken Broth 1/2 Cup; Asian Taste Chinkiang Vinegar 2 Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Premium Dark Soy Sauce 2 Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Hoisin Sauce  2 tsp; C&amp;amp;H Sugar 3 Tbsp; Flying Horse Tapioca Starch  1 1/2 tsp; Garlic 3 Cloves; Ginger 1 1/2Tbsp; Red Bell Pepper 1 pcs; Green Bell Pepper  1 pcs; Sichuan Peppercorns  1/2Tbsp; Peanuts 1/2 Cup; Green Onions 1 bunch; Mizuho 100% Pure Sesame Oil 2 Tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a bowl, mix chicken, soy sauce, shaoxing wine, baking soda and corstarch togther. Marinate for 10 minutes | In a seperate bowl, mix chicken stock, soy sauce, vinegar, shaoxing wine, dark soy sauce, hoisin sauce, sugar and cornstarch together as the sauce mix | In a skillet with medium high heat, add the chicken and stir fry until it&amp;#x27;s fully cooked and set it aside | In the pan with medium high heat, add in oil, garlic, ginger, red bell pepper, green bell pepper, sichuan pepperforns, and the sauce base, and bring it to a boil | Add in chicken, peanuts, and green onion to the pan. Mix well and ready to serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>234</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/44</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Spicy &amp; Sour Shredded Potato</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/c1c1e615b2274983a801d61d524f1650.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Potatoes 2 pcs; Sichuan Peppercorns 2 tsp; Dry Chili Peppers 8 pcs; Green Onions 1 bunch; Garlic 4 Cloves; Red Bell Pepper 1 pcs; C&amp;amp;H Sugar 1 tsp; Salt 1 tsp; Lee Kum Kee Soy Sauce 1 Tbsp; Asian Taste Chinkiang Vinegar 1 Tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Slice potatoes into thin slices. Soak in cold water. Drain and set aside | In a pan with medium high heat, add in oil, sichuan pepperforns, dry chili peppers, green onions (white part only), bellpepper, and shredded potato. Stir fry it | Add in sugar, salt, soy sauce, vinegar and scallion. Cook until it&amp;#x27;s tender and it&amp;#x27;s ready to serve</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>101</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/45</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Braised Chinese Mushroom with baby Bok Choy</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/5676f8e545014ccfb629c976a547f82d.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>35</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Asian Taste Dry Mushroom 2 1/2 oz; Baby Bok Choy 10 oz; Garlic 4 Cloves; Asian Taste Shaoxing Cooking Wine  1 Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Premium Dark Soy Sauce 1Tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Soy Sauce 1 1/2 tsp; Mizuho 100% Pure Sesame Oil 1/8 tsp; C&amp;amp;H Sugar 1 1/2 tsp; Lee Kum Kee White Pepper Powder 1/8 tsp; Flying Horse Tapioca Starch  1 1/2 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Place the dry mushroom in a bowl, our in boiling hot water, soak for 3 minutes | Drain the Mushroom water and save it | In another pot, bring water to boil, add in vegetable oil, and salt, quickly blanch the bak choy and move the bak choy to cold water | In a skillet, add in vegetable oil, garlic, and mushrooms. And add in shaoxing wine, mushroom water, dark soy sauce, oyster sauce, sesame oil, sugar, white pepper and the cornstarch slurry | Bring to boil and ready to eat! Pro tip: follow the video to see the plating instrustion</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>137</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/46</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Mapo Tofu</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/6cdf2b91eec84a1cb7351cb16401726e.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Vegetable Oil 1/4 cup &amp;amp; 1/4 cup; Dried Red Chili 10 pieces; Thai Chili 2 pieces; Ginger 3 tbsp; Garlic 4 tbsp; Ground Pork 1 1/2 pounds; Sichuan Peppercorn 1/2 tsp; Spicy Bean Sauce 2 tbsp; Chicken Stock 1 cup; Cornstarch 1 1/2 tsp; Water 1 1/2 tsp; Silken Tofu 1 pound; Sesame Oil 1/4 tsp; Sugar 1/4 tsp; Green Onion 1 piece</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Begin by heating the vegetable oil in a large skillet, then add in the dried red chilis and the Thai chilis. Toast the chilis then set aside. | Next add more oil to the pan along with ginger, garlic, and ground pork. Make sure to break up the ground pork as it cooks. | When the pork has browned add in Sichuan peppercorns, spicy bean sauce, and chicken stock then bring to a simmer. | Add the cornstarch slurry and the toasted chilis to the mixture and stir until thickened. | Add in the silken tofu, sesame oil, sugar, and green onions then stir to coat everything in the sauce. | Serve over rice with extra green onions for garnish.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>209</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/47</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Stir Fry Clams in Black Bean Sauce</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/f5b769465f3941e894cb75fdbe5353c5.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>120</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Fresh Clams 1/2 lbs.; Vegetable Oil 1 tsp; Green Bell Pepper 1 piece; Red Bell Pepper 1 piece; Ginger 2 tbsp; Green Onion 2 stalks; Garlic 2 cloves; Fermented Black Beans 1 tbsp; Shaoxing Wine 1 tbsp; Sugar 1 tsp; White Pepper 1/8 tsp; Sesame Oil 1 tsp; Cornstarch 1 tbsp; Water 1 tbsp; Cilantro 1 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat vegetable oil in a large pan with ginger, garlic, green onion, bell peppers, and fermented black beans. | Saute over medium heat and stir. | Add in uncooked fresh clams and shaoxing wine to the pan. | Cook the clams until they open to remove any fishy odor. | Add in sugar, white pepper, sesame oil, and cornstarch slurry. | Stir to combine and top with chopped cilantro.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>64</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/48</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese Lion&apos;s Head Meatball</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/e394ad0f4cb64210af871fd1eb262d8c.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>45</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Green Onions 2 stalks; Minced Pork 400 grams; Minced Chicken 100 grams; Shaoxing Wine 2 tbsp; Light soy sauce 2 tbsp; Salt ½ tsp; Sugar ½ tsp; Sesame oil ½ tsp; Eggs 1 piece; Cornstarch 1 tbsp; Water Chestnut 60 grams; Vegetable Oil (for frying)1-2 cups; Napa Cabbage 7 pieces; Dried Shitake Mushroom 6 pieces; Dried Shrimp ½ tbsp; White Pepper ¼ tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Prepare a tasty meatball mixture by combining minced pork, minced chicken, scallions, Shaoxing rice wine, light soy sauce, salt, sugar, sesame oil, egg, cornstarch, and minced water chestnuts. Mix well until sticky. | Divide the mixture into equal portions and shape each portion into a ball. | Deep fry the meatballs until golden brown and cooked through. Set aside. | In a separate pot, use the water in which dried shiitake mushrooms were soaked to simmer the fried meatballs, Napa cabbage, soaked mushrooms, dried shrimp (if using), salt, and ground white pepper. Simmer until cabbage is tender. | Serve the Lion’s Head Meatballs hot with the aromatic broth and enjoy the flavors of prosperity and good fortune!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>76</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/49</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Pork Char Siu</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/bf8bc0401c9949cdbbb2d5e26665e973.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>60</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Pork Shoulder 12 ounces; Char Siu Sauce 4 tbsp; Oyster Sauce 1 tbsp; Light Soy Sauce 1/2 tbsp; Chinese 5 Spice Powder 1/4 tsp; Chili Powder 1/2 tsp; Garlic 6 cloves; Ginger 8 pieces; Honey 2 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a large bowl whisk together Char Siu sauce, oyster sauce, light soy sauce, Chinese 5 Spice powder, chili powder, garlic, ginger, and honey until well combined. | Place the pork shoulder in a gallon size freezer bag. | Pour the Char Siu sauce mixture over the pork shoulder and close the bag. (Make sure to save some for basting) | Massage the mixture into the pork shoulder and refridgerate for 6 hours. | Place the pork on a baking rack over a cooking tray and fill the bottom of the tray with water. | Roast in the oven for 450F for 30-45 minutes. | Baste every 10-15 minutes with the remaining sauce. | Let the pork cool, then slice it and serve with rice.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>145</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/50</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Oyako Don</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/c14ecdab00cb4d4baec97c299ba9bc1d.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>45</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Chicken Thighs 12 ounces; Sake 1 tbsp; Eggs 4; Dashi Stock 1/2 cup; Soy Sauce 2 tbsp; Mirin 2 tbsp; Sugar 2 tsp; Onion 1/2; Green Onion 2 stalks; Parsley 1 tsp; Shichimi Togarashi 1/2 tsp; Sansho Pepper Powder 1/2 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Marinate chicken thigh pieces in sake for 5 minutes. | In a seperate bowl crack 4 eggs and mix, then set aside. | Mix dashi stock, soy sauce, mirin, and sugar in a small bowl. | Add sliced onions and dashi mixture to a large skillet, then bring it to a boil. | When the mixture has begun to boil add in the sake marinated chicken thighs. | Pour over the beaten eggs and cover with a lid until the eggs have set. | Top with chopped green onions and plate over rice. | Garnish with chopped parsley, shichimi togarashi, and sansho pepper powder.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>131</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/51</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Lu Rou Fan</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/f5986a708dfd4e488899f7d67f54403c.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>120</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Pork Belly 1 pound; Vegetable Oil 1 tbsp; Rock Sugar 1 ounce; Garlic 4 cloves; Shallots 2 pieces; Shitake Mushrooms 8 pieces; Chinese 5 Spice Powder 1 tsp; Shaoxong Wine 1/4 cup; Light Soy Sauce 3 tbsp; Dark Soy Sauce 2 tbsp; Water 2 cups; Star Anise  4 pieces; Szechuan Peppercorn 2 tsp; Bay Leaves 2 pieces; Cloves 6-8 pieces; Cinnamon Stick 1 piece; Ginger 6 slices; Orange Peel 1 piece; Hard Boiled Egg 4 eggs</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a wok heat up oil and rock sugar until the sugar begins to disolve, then add garlic and shallots. | When the garlic and shallots begin to soften add in shitake mushrooms, Chinese 5 spice, pork belly, Shaoxing wine, light soy sauce, dark soy sauce, and water. | Stir and bring to a boil. | Using a cheese cloth, add star anise, Szechuan peppercorns, bay leaves, cloves, cinnamon stick, ginger, and orange then tie off the spice bag. | Add the spice bag and hard boiled eggs to the wok, then cover with a lid letting the mixture simmer for 1-2 hours. Make sure to skim off the excess fat. | Remove the spice bag and serve over rice.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>136</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/52</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Hot &amp; Sour Soup</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/e6c1664724474137a525f0c32ab17805.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>45</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Pork Shoulder 4 ounces; Cornstarch 1 tbsp &amp;amp; 1/3 cup; Vegetable Oil 1 tbsp; Water 1 tbsp &amp;amp; 1/2 cup; Chicken Stock 2 quarts; Salt 1/4 tsp; Sugar 1/4 tsp; Dried Chili 3-4 pieces; Dried Shitake Mushroom 1/2 cup; Wood Ear Mushroom 1/2 cup; White Pepper 2 tsp; Light Soy Sauce 1 tbsp; Dark Soy Sauce 2 tsp; Sesame Oil 1 tsp; Bamboo Shoot 4 ounces; Dried Lily Flower 1/2 cup; Firm Tofu 4 ounces; Spiced Dry Tofu 4 ounces; White Vinegar 1/3 cup</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a small bowl mix together pork shoulder pieces, cornstarch, vegetable oil, and water then set aside. | Heat up chicken stock in a large pot and bring it to a boil. | Once the chicken stock is boiling add in the marinated pork shoulder pieces, salt, sugar, dried chilis, white pepper, light soy sauce, sesame oil, dark soy sauce, dried lily flower, dried shitake mushrooms, dried wood ear mushrooms, bamboo shoots, firm tofu, dried spiced tofu, and white vinegar. | Mix all the ingredients well, then slowly add in the cornstarch slurry while continuing to mix. | When the soup has thickened stir in one beaten egg until ribbons form. | Serve in a bowl and garnish with chopped green onions.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>158</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/53</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese Steamed Fish</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/fc2bf5d4770346ec97bf1c3d39174352.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Sea Bass (or fish of your choice) 1 pound; Fermented Black Beans 1 tbsp; Garlic 3 cloves; Ginger 1 piece; Green Onions 2-3 stalks; Vegetable Oil 1 tbsp; Sesame Oil 1/2 tsp; Lemon 1 piece; Cilantro 1 tbsp; Red Thai Chili 2-3 pieces</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a small bowl add in the fermented black beans, minced garlic, ginger slices, and green onions then mix together. | Pat dry your cleaned fish with a paper towel to remove the excess moisture. | Stuff the fermented black bean mixture inside the cavity of the fish. | Drizzle the fish with vegetable oil, sesame oil, and the juice of half a lemon. | Steam the fish for 10-15 minutes using a steamer or by creating a steaming rack using foil. | When the fish has finished cooking serve with more green onions, sliced red Thai chilis, and cilantro.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>88</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/54</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Beef Pad See Ew</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/64586e9a20bc4aa3b8fe8c83bad21928.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>25</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Flank Steak 8 ounces; Vegetable oil 1 tsp + 4 tbsp; Fish sauce 1 tsp; Garlic 3 cloves; White pepper 1/2 tsp; Chinese broccoli 1 bunch; Cornstarch 1 tsp; Soy sauce 1 tsp + 2 tsp; Dark soy sauce 1 tbsp; Wide rice noodles 1 pound; Sugar 1/2 tsp; Oyster sauce 1 tbsp; Eggs 2 pieces</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a bowl add the dark soy sauce, vegetable oil, and cornstarch, to the flank steak and mix until the beef is completely coated. Set aside. | Heat a wok on high and oil evenly to coat the pan. Then sear the steak until it is 80% cooked through, and transfer it back to the marinade bowl. | Add more oil to the wok and stir in the garlic and Chinese broccoli. Make sure to stir constantly to prevent the garlic from burning. | Cook the wide rice noodles according to the package and set aside. (Remember, 8 ounces of dried noodles will rehydrate to 16 ounces.) | Add the cooked noodles and the cooked steak, then stir again. | Push the mixture to one side to let the empty side of the wok heat for 10 seconds. Then add two beaten eggs and scramble. | Next, combine oyster sauce, sugar, soy sauce, dark soy sauce, fish sauce, and white pepper in a small bowl. Pour the sauce into the wok and make sure everything is evenly coated. | Stir-fry the mixture for another 1-2 minutes until everything is mixed well and serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>153</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/55</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Kung Pao Shrimp</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/ad06a04e014947d2866ebb78b2f7dfdd.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>P&amp;amp;D Shrimp 1 pound; Canola Oil 1 tsp + 1 tsp + 3 tbsp; Shaoxing wine 1 tsp; Salt 1/4 tsp; White pepper 1/8 tsp; Cornstarch 1/2 tsp + 1 tsp; Rice wine vinegar 1 tbsp; Light soy sauce 1 tbsp; Sugar 1 tsp; Sichuan peppercorn powder 1/2 tsp; Dark soy sauce 1/2 tsp; Garlic 3 cloves; Ginger 1 tbsp; Dried red chilies 2-4 pieces; Green onions 6 pieces; Raw Peanuts 1 cup</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat 1 teaspoon of oil in a pan over medium heat. Add the raw peanuts and toast until golden brown, then set aside. | In a large bowl add the shrimp, oil, Shaoxing wine, salt, and white pepper powder. Then set aside for 15 minutes and mix in the cornstarch right before cooking. | Heat the pan over high heat then add 2 tbsp of oil, followed by the shrimp and quickly sear the shrimp on both sides. Once they turn pink remove from the pan and set aside. | Lower the heat to and add the remaining tablespoon of oil, garlic, ginger, chilies, and scallions. Cook for 1-2 minutes, until fragrant. | Increase the heat to high, and add the shrimp back to the wok. Stir-fry for 30 seconds. | In a bowl, combine water, rice wine vinegar, light soy sauce, sugar, cornstarch, Sichuan peppercorn powder, and dark soy sauce. | Add the sauce to the pan, and stir-fry for another minute until it thickens. Next add the peanuts, then mix until everything is coated, and serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>75</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/56</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Hong Kong Style Curry Fish Ball</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/7ec4d7043900483ea2daf8da4e666c3e.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>25</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Fish Ball 2-3 lbs; Lee Kum Kee Sauce for Hong Kong Style Fish Balls 1 jar; Lee Kum Kee’s Premium Oyster Sauce 1 tbsp; Water 4 cups</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Begin by boiling the frozen fish balls in a wok. | Heat up the wok, add Lee Kum Kee Sauce for Hong Kong Style Fish Balls and stir-fry over medium heat for 2 minutes. | Add Lee Kum Kee’s Premium Oyster Sauce, mix well and then add water. Turn up the heat and bring it to a boil, then add the fish balls. | Turn down the heat and simmer for about 20 minutes (stirring constantly midway to prevent burning). | For an extra kick, add Lee Kum Kee Fiery Hot Dried Shrimp Chili Oil as an additional seasoning.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>54</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/57</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Easy Rice Cooker Pork Fried Rice</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/93b0480bcdea4e418d90533ecc4d4b6c.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>White Rice 3 cups; Tomato (diced) 1 piece; Sesame oil 1 tsp; Soy sauce 3 tbsp; Edamame 1/4 cup; Carrots (diced) 1/4 cup; Mushrooms (diced) 1/4 cup; Corn 1/4 cup; Chinese sausage (diced) 1/4 cup; Salt to taste</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a rice cooker add 3 cups of washed white rice, then cover the rice with 4 1/2 cups of water or until it reaches the number 3 on the water line. | Add in 1 tsp sesame oil, 3 tbsp soy sauce, and salt to the rice then stir. | Now add in the diced tomato, diced Chinese sausage, diced mushroom, diced carrots, corn, and edamame to the rice then cook. | Once the rice cooker finishes it&amp;#x27;s cooking cycle stir all the ingredients together until everything is mixed well. Serve in a bowl and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>115</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/58</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Vietnamese Shaking Beef (BÒ LÚC LẮC)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/eed9eb4b8a8442b2b27c1784f1502498.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>35</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Beef steak 1 lbs; Soy sauce 1 tbsp; Oyster sauce 2 tbsp; Minced garlic 4 cloves; Sugar 2 tsp; Yellow onion 1 piece; Green onion 3 stalks; Salt 1/8 tsp; Pepper 1/8 tsp; Neutral cooking oil 2 tbsp; MSG (optional) to taste</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cut the beef into 1 inch cubes and add soy sauce, oyster sauce, sugar, minced garlic, salt, pepper and msg. Mix well and set aside. | In a hot pan add neutral oil and sear the cubes of beef. Make sure the pan is not overcrowded. (Cook the beef in small batches at a time if needed.) | Make sure the beef is seared on all sides by shaking the pan to flip the cubes, or using a spatula or tongs. | Next, add the onions to the beef and continue shaking and stirring until the onions are just tender, about 1-2 minutes. | Serve with rice or  over a bed of greens with sliced tomatoes and cucumbers!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>119</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/59</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Sriracha Mayo Poke Bruschetta</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/0e0094f0d7c047c5b499bd08ac5ab8fa.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>French baguette 1 loaf; Raw Salmon 4 oz; Raw Tuna 4 oz; Imitation crab with mayo (pre-mixed) 3 oz; Avocado (sliced) 1/2 piece; Masago 2 tbsp; Cucumber (sliced) 2 oz; Tomato (sliced) 2 oz; Green onion 1 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee&amp;#x27;s Premium Oyster Sauce 2 tbsp; Mirin 4 tsp; Rice vinegar 1/2 tsp; Lee Kum Kee Pure Sesame Oil 1 tsp; Lee Kum Kee Sriracha Mayo 2 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cut baguette into slices and toast lightly. Add the oyster sauce, mirin, rice vinegar, and sesame oil in a small bowl and mix sauce well, then set aside. | Dice salmon and tuna. | Mix the diced salmon and tuna with green onion and sesame, then stir in the sauce. | Place tomato, avocado, and cucumber slices on toasted baguette. Add fish mixture and imitation crab on top. | Drizzle each with the sauce and Sriracha mayo. Finally, top with masago and serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>46</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/60</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese Lobster Noodles (Lobster Yee Mein)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/9a8e660ad2734acd954b4aef3e568295.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>60</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Lobster tail 12 oz; Cornstarch 1 cup + 1 tbsp; Salt 1 tsp; White pepper 1 tsp; Canola oil 1 cup; Oyster sauce 1 1/2 tbsp; Soy sauce 1 1/2 tbsp; Sugar 1/2 tbsp; Shaoxing wine 1 tbsp; Sesame oil 1 tsp; Chicken broth 1/4 cup + 1 cup; Green onion 1 bunch; Garlic 4-5 cloves; Ginger 1 tbsp; Noodles (E-Yu, Yi Mein, or Shanghai noodles) 16 oz; Water 3 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Begin by cutting the lobster tails into 2 inch pieces making sure to leave the shell on. Now mix the sauce. Start by combining oyster sauce, soy sauce, sugar, white pepper, shaoxing wine, sesame oil, and chicken broth then set aside. | On a large plate mix cornstarch, salt, and white pepper. Then coat the lobster pieces in the seasoned cornstarch, and shake off any excess. | Next, cook the noodles in boiling water. Then after draining, immediately rinse the noodles with cold water to remove excess starch and prevent over cooking. | In a wok or large pan heat 1 cup of canola oil to about 350F then fry the lobster pieces until the lobster is bright red and cooked through. (about 1 minute) | Now in a large pan or wok, add 1 tbsp of oil and stir fry garlic, ginger, and scallion whites until fragrant. Then add in the fried lobster pieces and stir fry. | Add sauce and stir over high heat, then combine chicken stock and heat until boiling, then simmer for 4-5 minutes to reduce. | Add scallion greens then add cornstarch slurry and stir until the sauce has thickened. Mix in noodles in and serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>65</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/61</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Char Siu Pork Fried Rice</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/05b811ca06e44b439d041ab9f3cdc28b.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Canola oil 2 tbsp; Shallots (diced) 1 oz; Eggs (beaten) 2 pieces; White rice 1 lbs; Pork Char Siu (diced) 4 oz; Green onion 1 oz; Oyster sauce 2 tbsp; Soy sauce 1 1/2 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Using a hot wok, stir-fry diced shallots in 2 tbsp oil until fragrant. | Next, add in beaten eggs to the wok and scramble. | Mix in cooked rice, diced char siu, green onions, soy sauce, and oyster sauce. | Cook until everything has heated through and serve! | Optional Seasoning: Add Lee Kum Kee Fiery Hot Dried Shrimp Chili Oil or Lee Kum Kee Chiu Chow Style Chili Crisp Oil as an to enhance the flavor.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>77</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/62</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Boiled Seafood Platter</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/b2c3e7019d7044fdb6289bc98b573c76.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>40</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Shell-On Shrimp 10 oz; Mussels (on half shell) 8 pieces; Squid rings 6 oz; Crab sticks 4 pieces; Fresh scallops 6 oz; Vegetable oil 4 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Minced Garlic 3 tbsp; Minced millet pepper 2 tbsp; Green onion (for garnish) 2 tbsp; Lemon (for garnish) 2 slices; Cilantro (for garnish) 2 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Seasoned Soy Sauce 6 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Pure Sesame Oil 1 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cook the seafood in separate batches in boiling water, draining each well and placing onto a plate. | Heat the oil in a pot and quickly stir-fry the Lee Kum Kee Minced Garlic and millet pepper until fragrant. Drizzle the mixture over the cooked seafood. | Scatter chopped scallion, lemon and cilantro over the dish, and drizzle the seafood with Lee Kum Kee Seasoned Soy Sauce for Seafood and Lee Kum Kee Pure Sesame Oil then serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>37</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/63</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Spicy Korean Pork Bulgogi</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/aad98b9be20741ae8dcb9edbe3bdd524.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>35</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Pork belly (sliced) 2 lbs; Gochujang 1/4 cup; Light soy sauce 2 tbsp; Sugar 1 tbsp; Gochugaru (Korean chili flakes) 2 tbsp; Black pepper 1 tsp; Garlic (minced) 4-6 cloves; Ginger (minced) 1 tbsp; Sesame oil 1 tbsp; Yellow onion 1 piece; Green onions 4 stalks; Canola oil 1 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a bowl mix together the gochujang, light soy sauce, sugar, gochugaru (Korean chili flakes), black pepper, salt, garlic, ginger, and sesame oil. Then set aside. | Next, add in the sliced pork belly, sliced yellow onion, and green onions to the mixture. Stir everything until the pork is covered in the sauce, then marinate it for 15 minutes. | In a large pan heat 1 tbsp of cooking oil over medium heat then add in the pork. Cook the pork for about 3-5 minutes until the pork has cooked through. | Serve over white rice and garnish with extra green onions, then enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>140</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/64</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Beef Pad Thai</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/58b8f81f78404c6ba5801bded051c745.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Kikkoman Noodle Kit with Sauce Pad Thai 1 pack; Canola Oil 2 tsp; Ground Beef ¾ pound; Snap Peas 2 cups; Shredded Carrots 2 cups; Green Onions ½ cup; Peanuts 1 tsp; Limes 1-2 wedges</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Boil noodles until they have soften and then drain. | Heat oil in a large skillet, then cook and crumble beef until browned. | Add snap peas, carrots, and scallions; stir until peas are vibrant. | Mix in sauce, noodles, and half of the reserved cooking liquid then simmer until veggies are tender. | Serve hot with peanuts and lime wedges.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>74</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/65</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Thai Duck Salad (Larb Ped)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/02b4c8573eec41dc9fdddd76b830db57.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>60</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Duck 12 oz; Lime juice 1 1/2 tbsp; White sugar 1/2 tsp; Fish sauce 1/2 tsp; Red chili flakes 1/2 tsp; Toasted rice powder 1/2 tsp; Green onions 1 bunch; Cilantro 1 bunch; Shallots 2 pieces; Kaffir lime leaves 4-6 pieces; Dried chili 4-6 pieces</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Separate the duck meat from the skin, then mince the meat and cut the skin into small pieces. Fry the duck skin until crispy and transfer on to a paper towl to absorb excess grease. | In the duck fat, fry the dried chilies, kaffir lime leaves, and shallots until aromatic. Place the aromatics on a paper towl to drain excess oil and set aside. | Using the same pan add in the minced duck meat and fry until cooked through, then set aside. | In a large bowl mix together lime juice, sugar, fish sauce, red chili flakes, and toasted rice powder. | Add the cooked minced duck meat, green onions, cilantro, and shallots to the dressing. Mix well. | Garnish with the fried dried chilies, fried kaffir lime leaves, fried shallots, crispy duck skin, green onions, and cilantro. Serve jasmine rice, sticky rice, or in lettuce wraps!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>34</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/66</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Filipino Salmon in Coconut Milk (Ginataang Salmon)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/445cc16cd79a46d4968186674ede0390.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>40</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Salmon steak 1 1/2 lbs; Coconut cream 2 cups; Garlic (minced) 3 cloves; Ginger (minced) 1 tbsp; Long green chili 3 pieces; Red chili 3 pieces; Yellow onion (sliced) 1 piece; Cane vinegar 1/4 cup; Fish sauce 1 tbsp; Ground black pepper 1/4 tsp; Water 1/2 cup; Canola oil 1 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat cooking oil in a medium frying pan, then add in the salmon, long green chili, Thai red chili, garlic, ginger, onion, and ground black pepper. | Next, add cane vinegar and water to the pan. Simmer on low heat for about 2 minutes then add in the coconut cream to the salmon. | Continue to simmer on low for another 20 minutes until the liquid has reduced to half and the salmon has cooked through. | Garnish with extra long green chili and Thai red chili, then serve as it is or with white rice!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>35</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/67</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Japanese Glass Noodle Salad</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/8239302f38c542d6b542bd673219f95d.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Bean thread noodles 1 pack; Cucumber 1 piece; Carrot 1 piece; Rice vinegar 2 tbsp; Soy sauce 2 tbsp; Sugar 1 tbsp; Sesame oil 1 tbsp; Toasted sesame seeds 2 tsp; Chili flakes 1/4 tsp; Green onion 1 stalk</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Begin by boiling the bean thread noodles for 3-4 minutes, then drain and set aside. | Thinly slice the carrot diagonally, then cut into even matchsticks. | Next cut the cucumber in half, remove the seeds, then slice and cut into even matchsticks. | Make the dressing by combinging soy sauce, rice vinegar, sugar, and sesame oil then stir until everything is combined. | Cut the cooked bean thread noodles, then add the cucumber, carrot, dressing, sesame seeds, chilli flakes and mix well so that everything is coated. | Mix everything again before serving, and garnish with the chopped green onion.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>131</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/68</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Thai Red Curry Shrimp</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/11bc1506ee1a42c5b6377d933a732935.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>45</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Shrimp (peeled &amp;amp; deveined) 1 lbs; Olive oil 2 tbsp; Yellow onion 1 piece; Ginger (minced) 1 tbsp; Garlic (minced) 2-3 cloves; Bell pepper (red, orange, or green) 1 piece; Red curry paste 2 tbsp; Coconut milk 1 can; Salt 1 tsp; Ground black pepper 1 tsp; Lime 1-2 pieces; Cilantro 1 bunch</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a large pan, heat olive oil on medium heat then add the onion slices and cook until the onions are softened. Next add ginger, garlic, salt, and black pepper and cook for 1 minute. | Then add the red curry paste, to the pan and stir together. Add the bell pepper and cook until softened, about 1-2 minutes. Afterwards add the coconut milk, then fill the can about halfway with water and bring the mixture to a gentle simmer. | Season the peeled and deveined shrimp with salt and pepper then add it to the pot. Cover and simmer for another 1-2 minutes, or until the shrimp is cooked through. | Garnish with lime juice, lime wedge, and cilantro then serve over white rice!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>96</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/69</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Vietnamese Rice Noodle Salad with Chicken</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/88c7e947044742b1962191470ec46c11.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>90</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Boneless chicken thighs 1 lbs; Garlic 2 cloves + 3 cloves; Lime 1 piece + 1 piece; Fish sauce 2 tbsp + 1/4 cup; Soy sauce 1 tbsp; Brown sugar 2 tbsp; Vegetable oil 1 tbsp; Rice vinegar 2 tbsp; White sugar 3 tbsp; Red Thai chili pepper 1 piece; Vermicelli rice noodles 1 pack; Bean sprouts 2 cups; Carrot 1 piece; Cucumber 1 piece; Mint 1 bunch; Cilantro 1 bunch; Romaine lettuce 1 bunch</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Make the marinade for the chicken by mixing together 2 cloves minced garlic, 1 lime (juiced), 2 tablespoons fish sauce, 1 tablespoon soy sauce, 2 tablespoons brown sugar, and 1 tablespoon vegetable oil. | Add the boneless chicken thighs to the marinade and set aside for 10 minutes to 1 hour. | Prepare the Vermicelli rice noodles according to the package instructions, then drain and rinse with cold water. Set aside. | Make the Nuoc Cham sauce by combining 3 cloves minced garlic, 1 lime (juiced), 2 tablespoons rice vinegar, 1/4 cup fish sauce, 3 tablespoons sugar, 1 red Thai chili (or substitute 2 teaspoons Sriracha), 1/2 cup cold water and stir until the sugar has dissolved. | Heat vegetable oil in a frying pan over medium high heat and sear the chicken for until cooked through. (around 3-5 minutes) | In a large bowl mix the rice noodles with bean sprouts, julienned carrots and cucumber, romaine lettuce, mint, and cilantro. Then slice the chicken thighs and add to the salad. Serve with Nuoc Cham sauce and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>84</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/70</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Sichuan Wontons in Chili Oil</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/fef6c19c50b440a0a06de1e327c93fc0.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>10</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Lee Kum Kee Chiu Chow Style Chili Crisp Oil 1 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Chili Oil 1 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Seasoning Soy Sauce 1 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Pure Sesame Oil 1 tsp; Lee Kum Kee Selected Seasoned Aromatic Vinegar 2 tsp; Lee Kum Kee Minced Garlic 2 tsp; Sugar 1 tsp; Pork and shrimp wontons 6-8 pieces</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cook the pork wontons in boiling water, drain and place on a plate or bowl. | Combine all the seasoning ingredients and pour over the wontons. | Sprinkle with chopped green onions and serve.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>106</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/71</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Garlic Sesame Tofu</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/c6f5991879014cecac4f39172739ce33.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>45</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Soy sauce 1 tbsp + 1/3 c; Extra firm tofu 1 pack; Cornstarch 1 tbsp + 1 tbsp; Panko bread crumbs 3 tbsp; Sesame oil 2 tsp; Rice vinegar 1 tsp; Honey 3 tbsp; Water 4 tbsp; Garlic 5 cloves; Vegetable oil 1 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Drain the excess liquid from the tofu using a paper towel. | Cut the tofu into 1 inch cubes and add to a large bowl. Toss with 1 tbsp soy sauce, 1 tbsp cornstarch, and 3 tbsp panko breadcrumbs until all pieces are evenly coated. | Add the tofu cubes to the baking tray and bake for 30-35 minutes at 400F until golden brown. | Make the sauce by adding garlic with 1 tbsp vegetable oil in a small saute pan for 2-3 minutes or until lightly browned. Then add in 1/3 c. soy sauce, 3 tbsp honey, 1 tsp rice vinegar, 2 tbsp of water, 2 tsp sesame oil, and mix well. | To thicken the sauce whisk together 1 tbsp cornstarch and another 2 tbsp of water in a bowl and add to the mixture. Heat over low heat for 3-5 minutes or until the sauce bubbles and thickens. | When the tofu is crispy, toss the tofu cubes with the sauce. Serve over rice with steamed broccoli or enjoy as is!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>90</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/72</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Thai Green Papaya Salad</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/599e69d0b28a4c6b9dea90dd00967de6.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>25</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Green papaya (julienned) 1 1/2 c; Garlic 2 cloves; Thai chili pepper 2-4 pieces; Palm sugar 1 1/2 tbsp; Long beans 2-3 pieces; Roasted peanuts 3 tbsp; Dried shrimp 1 tbsp; Lime 1 piece; Tamarind paste 2 tsp; Fish sauce 1 1/2 tbsp; Grape tomato 1/2 c</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Start by peeling and julienning the green papaya, then soak the papaya in cold water. Drain the soaked papaya well and place in a bowl lined with 2 layers of paper towel to absorb excess water. | Using a mortar and pestle, pound garlic and chilies until there are no more big chunks (pieces of chili skin are fine). | Add palm sugar and mash with the pestle until it turns into a wet paste and all the chunks are dissolved. | Add long beans and pound just until they&amp;#x27;re broken. | Add dried shrimp and peanuts and pound to break the peanuts up slightly. | Add fish sauce, tamarind paste, and lime juice then stir. | Add the dressing and sliced grape tomatoes to the shredded papaya. | Mix everything together until well incorporated, and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>79</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/73</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Udon Noodle Soup</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/a2727c76cad3491eae8db1f0165b9215.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Water 2 cups; Udon noodles 1 pack; Soy sauce 2 tbsp; Sugar 1/4 tsp; Mirin 1 tbsp; Dashi powder 1/2 tbsp; Tsuyu 1 Tbsp; Green onion 1 stalk; Furikake 1/8 tsp; Tofu skins (or bean curd) 1-2 sheets</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a medium pan add water, instant dashi powder, soy sauce, sugar, mirin, and tsuyu. Then bring to a simmer over medium heat for about 2-3 minutes. | Once the broth has begun simmering add the udon noodles directly into the hot broth. Use a spoon to gently loosen the noodles and cook for 1-3 minutes until the noodles have softened. | Transfer to a large bowl, then garnish with green onion, furikake seaweed seasoning, fried bean curd, and narutomaki (fishcake). Serve and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>75</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/74</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Quick Spicy Korean Noodle Soup</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/ac7264b7ea024f1888958fdddd11126a.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Chicken broth 4 cups; Kimchi 2/3 cups; Kimchi juice (from the container) 2 tbsp; Gochujang 3 tbsp; Shaoxing wine 1 tbsp; Ginger 1 piece; Garlic 1-2 cloves; Egg noodles 8 oz; Choi sum 4 pieces; Carrot 1 piece; Sesame oil 2 1/2 tsp; Green onion 1 stalk</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a large stock pot add in 4 cups chicken broth, 2/3 cup cabbage kimchi, 2 tbsp kimchi juice, 3 tbsp gochujang, 1 tbsp Shaoxing wine, 2 slices ginger, and 2 garlic gloves. Then cook on mediun heat for about 10 minutes until the broth begins to simmer. | Next, add choi sum stems and carrot to the broth, then simmer for another 2 minutes. When the stems and carrot soften a bit add choi sum leaves and sesame oil, then simmer for 1 minute. | Cook the egg noodles in boiling water according to the packet directions. Then drain the noodles and quickly rinse it under tap water to remove extra starch. (Make sure to shake off excess water well.) | Begin plating the noodles in bowls and top with the sauteed vegetables. Pick the garlic and ginger out of the broth, then broth pour over the noodles and vegetables. Garnish with green onions and serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>43</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/75</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Easy Curry Laksa Soup</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/cf5f1b6125614e65b21f55f622ffc70d.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>40</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Vegetable oil 2 tbsp; Thai red curry paste 2 tbsp; Curry powder 2 tbsp; Boneless chicken thighs 6 oz; Coconut milk 1 can (13.5 fl oz); Chicken stock 4 c; Peel &amp;amp; deveined shrimp 14 oz; Fish ball 6 oz; Tofu puff 6-8 pieces; Fish sauce 2 tbsp; Sugar 1 tsp; Egg noodles (can use Vermicelli or Wheat noodles) 1/2 lbs; Bean sprouts 1/2 c; Egg 1-2 pieces; Cilantro 1 bunch</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat the oil in a large pan over medium-high heat then add the curry paste and cook, stirring, for a minute or until fragrant. Stir in the curry powder, then add the chicken thighs and cook for 1-2 minutes. Next add coconut milk and chicken stock to the mixture. Bring the soup to a low boil and simmer for about 5 minutes. | Now add the shrimp, fish balls, and tofu puffs to the soup. Simmer for a another few minutes or until the shrimp is fully cooked. | Add fish sauce and sugar. (Season to taste, add extra if needed.) Ladle your laksa soup broth over the noodles and garnish with bean sprouts, a boiled egg and cilantro.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>41</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/76</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Thai Coconut Squash Soup</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/e13aab99ef634231983a6474fc335ef6.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>25</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Vegetable oil 2 tbsp; Thai red curry paste 3 tbsp; Garlic 1-2 cloves; Yellow onion 1 piece; Coconut milk 1 can (13.5 fl oz); Chicken stock 2 1/2 c; Butternut squash (can use pumpkin or kabocha) 1 piece; Fish sauce 1 tbsp; Cilantro 1 bunch; Fried shallots 1 tsp; Red Thai chili 1 piece; Roti 1 piece</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat oil in a large pot over medium high heat. Add onion and garlic, cook for 2 minutes until soft. | Add curry paste and cook for 2 minutes until fragrant. | Add squash and stir to coat in the flavors for around 2 minutes. | Set aside 1/4 cup coconut milk for garnish. Add stock, remaining coconut milk and fish sauce. Bring to simmer then reduce heat to medium and simmer for 8 minutes until the pumpkin is soft. | Next, blend the soup mixture until everything is smooth and well incorporated. | Ladle the soup into bowls and garnish with fried shallots, red Thai chili slices, and cilantro. Serve with roti bread and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>66</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/77</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Tteokbokki with Ramen</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/4836f30a7b414c4195648e3977192d75.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Chicken stock 3 cups; Korean rice cakes (Tteok) 1 cup; Instant ramen 1 pack; Fish cake (cut in small pieces) 2 sheets; Green onion 3 stalks; Shredded cabbage 1 cup; Boiled eggs 1-2 pieces; Soy sauce 2 tbsp; Sugar 1 1/2 tbsp; Chili flakes 1 tbsp; Minced garlic 2 cloves; Honey 2 tbsp; Gochujang 3 tbsp; Sesame seeds 1/2 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a small bowl mix together the soy sauce, sugar, garlic, chili flakes, Gochujang paste, and honey. | Add chicken stock to a large pot, then when it begins to simmer add in the Gochujang sauce and the rice cakes (Tteok). Boil for about 7 minutes. | Next, add in the fish cakes, ramen, shredded cabbage, and green onions. Stir well to make sure everything is covered in the sauce. | Cook the mixture until the ramen noodles soften, then add in hard boiled eggs. | When the ramen noodles have fully cooked, serve in a bowl and garnish with extra green onions and sesame seeds. Enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>94</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/78</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Kabocha with Pork and Mushrooms</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/a22a0b2d62ff4801a97f02795d3ac4db.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Kabocha squash 1 piece; Green onions 2 stalks; Minced garlic 2 tsp; Enoki mushrooms 1 pack; Avocado oil 2 tbsp; Salt 1 tsp; Ground pork 1/2 lbs; Chicken broth 2 tbsp; Sesame oil 3 tsp; Shirataki noodles 1 pack; Soy sauce 2 tbsp; Rice vinegar 1 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat a large skillet, then add avocado oil, garlic, and white parts of green onion, and salt on medium heat until fragrant. | Next add ground pork to the skillet and season with salt and use a wooden spoon to break up the meat. Cook through until it’s no longer pink. | Add squash, mushrooms, sesame oil, soy sauce, and rice vinegar then lower the heat. Stir thoroughly, then add 2 tbsp stock and cover with a lid to simmer until the squash is tender. | Drain and rinse the shirataki noodles according to the package instructions. Then add the noodles to the pan and stir to coat the noodles with the meat and sauce. | Turn off the heat. Drizzle with more sesame oil and garnish with more green green onions, then enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>23</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/79</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese Pumpkin Omelet</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/99a08b61e9dd44d8a41347e2fbf1ba24.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Kabocha 1 piece; Green onions 2 stalks; Eggs 3 pieces; Black pepper 1/2 tsp; Shaoxing wine 1 tbsp; Salt 1/2 tsp; Oil 2 tbsp; Sesame seeds 1/2 tsp; Soy Sauce (for dipping) 2 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a large bowl, beat the eggs and season with salt, pepper, and cooking wine. Mix in the pumpkin and chives, then set aside. | Heat oil in a 10-inch non-stick pan over medium-low, tilting to coat evenly. Once warm, pour in the mixture and spread it out with a spatula. | Cover and cook for 5 minutes, then flip with a plate and cook uncovered for another 4-5 minutes. | Top with toasted sesame seeds and serve with soy sauce for dipping.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>17</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/80</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Mung Bean Soup</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/c50995fb1b0a4853b8e1988673919765.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>90</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Dried mung beans 1 cup; Dried lily bulb 1/3 cup; Glutinous rice 2 tbsp; Sago 1/2 cup; Sugar 1 tbsp; Water 8 cups</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>First, rinse the mung beans, dried lily bulb pieces, and sweet rice under cold water. Then add them to a large bowl and cover with water. Soak for 8 hours or overnight. | Drain the beans, lily bulb, and rice, then transfer to a large pot with 8 cups of water. Next bring it to a boil, cover, and simmer for about 1 hour, or until the beans are very soft. | Add the sago to the soup after it’s been cooking for about 40 minutes. It will take about 20 minutes for the sago to cook (it will be translucent). | Now add in your sugar to taste. You can also refrain from adding sugar at this point, and each person can sweeten their individual bowls as they like.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>25</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/81</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Asian Twist Charcuterie Board</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/2a092a3874824fe4a432d4c0e32275b8.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Roasted chestnuts 1 cup; Homemade pickles 1 cup; Chinese pickled cucumbers 1 cup; Brie cheese 1 wedge; Sesame mochi 4-6 pieces; Pepperjack cheese 4-6 pieces; Gyoza 4-6 pieces; Black pepper scone 2-4 pieces; Wasabi peas 1 cup; Grapes 1 cup; Egg roll cookies 6-8 pieces; Sugar snap peas 1/2 cup; Dried apricot 1/2 cup; Chips 1 cup; Mandarins 4-6 pieces; Pineapple 4-6 pieces; Papaya 1 piece</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Arrange smaller bites and sauces in small bowls, then group the other ingredients on a large wooden cutting board or platter to serve.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>12</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/82</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Sichuan Green Beans</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/093ce0cce44849caa9563cb8ac0cb209.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Green beans 1 lbs; Avocado oil 2 tbsp; Ground pork 1/4 lbs; Sichuan peppercorn 1/4 tsp; Dried chili pepper 2-4 pieces; Garlic 3 cloves; Ginger 1 tsp; Shaoxing wine 2 tbsp; Soy sauce 1 tbsp; Sugar 1 tsp; Salt 1/2 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat 1 tablespoon of oil in a large nonstick skillet over medium-high heat. Add green beans and a pinch of salt, stirring to coat with oil. Spread beans to minimize overlap and flip every 15 seconds. Cook 6-8 minutes until some beans are browned and softened. For a softer texture, cook 10-12 minutes until charred, lowering heat if needed. Transfer beans to a plate. | Add 1 tablespoon oil, ground pork, and ground Sichuan peppercorns to the skillet. Cook through, breaking the pork into small pieces. | Next, add dried chili pepper, garlic, and ginger. Stir briefly, then return green beans to the skillet. Add Shaoxing wine, soy sauce, and sugar, then cook until sauce is mostly absorbed (1-2 minutes). | Lower heat, taste, and adjust salt if needed. Serve hot as a side or main dish, and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>76</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/83</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese 5 Spice Cranberry Sauce</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/8788fb3de66e420bbebb8a65691917f8.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Water 1 cup; Port Wine 2/3 cup; Brown sugar 3/4 cup; Dried cherries 1/3 cup; Fresh or frozen cranberries 12 oz; Orange juice 1-2 tbsp; Orange zest 1-2 tbsp; Red wine vinegar 1 tbsp; Chinese 5 spice powder 1 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a medium saucepan, combine water, brown sugar, port, and dried cherries over medium heat, stirring until the sugar dissolves. | Increase to high heat, add fresh or frozen cranberries, and bring to a boil. Reduce to medium heat and simmer for 10 minutes until some cranberries pop and the liquid reduces slightly. Lower the heat if it boils too vigorously. Then stir in orange juice, zest, vinegar, and Chinese 5 spice. If you like a more jammy cranberry sauce continue to cook the cranberries on low for an additional 5 to 10 minutes. | Transfer to a heat-safe container, let cool, and refrigerate until ready to use!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>16</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/84</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Steamed Eggs</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/e02fb3f6e0a94b42880e482a3e65e2be.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>10</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Eggs 3 pieces; Water 1.5 cups; Chicken broth 1.5 cups; Salt 1 tsp; Sesame oil 1 tsp; Green onion 2 stalks</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Crack 3 eggs into a liquid measuring cup and note the volume. Transfer to a bowl, add salt, and beat for 1 minute. Measure equal volumes of water and broth, add to the eggs, and whisk in sesame oil until combined. | Strain the mixture into a heatproof dish and place inside a steamer. | Boil water in a steamer. Steam the eggs over high heat for 3 minutes, then turn off the heat and leave covered for 14 minutes. | Garnish with scallions and more sesame oil, then serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>87</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/85</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Tomato Tofu</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/a2618d4b493d4053afe62c2fae678671.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Avocado oil 2 tbsp; Green onion 1 bunch; Tomato 1 lbs; Shaoxing wine 1 tbsp; Water 1/2 c; Sugar 1 tbsp; Salt 1/2 tsp; Oyster sauce 1 tbsp; Soy sauce 2 tsp; Sesame oil 1 tsp; White pepper 1/2 tsp; Cornstarch 2 tsp; Soft tofu 1-2 packs</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat a stainless steel wok or skillet over high heat. Add neutral oil and the white parts of the scallions. Stir for 15 seconds, then add the tomatoes. | Stir-fry for 2 minutes, then add Shaoxing wine around the pan’s edge. | Add water (or stock), sugar, salt, vegetarian oyster sauce, light soy sauce, sesame oil, and white pepper. Simmer for 1 minute until tomatoes soften. | Prepare a cornstarch slurry and stir it into the sauce to thicken. Add tofu, gently mixing to avoid breaking it. | Reduce heat to medium, cover, and cook for 2 minutes until the tomatoes and sauce are thickened. Adjust with more slurry if needed. | Uncover, stir in scallions, and season with salt and sugar to taste. Serve with jasmine rice and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>38</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/86</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Microwave Hot Pot</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/bc475284de7d45d2b69ead54b4fc8168.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Enoki mushrooms 100g; Carrot 1/2 piece; Cherry tomatoes 5-6 pieces; Bok choy (or Asian greens of choice) 1 cup; Cabbage 200g; Thinly sliced beef 200g; Garlic 1 tsp; Ginger 1 tsp; Soy sauce 2 tbsp; Dashi or miso stock 500ml</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Assemble the Hotpot: Layer enoki mushrooms, carrot slices, cherry tomatoes, green vegetables, cabbage, and shabu shabu beef in a large microwave-safe container. | Mix garlic, ginger, soy sauce, and dashi or miso stock. Pour it over the ingredients. | Cover with a microwave-safe lid or plate and microwave on high for 6-8 minutes until the beef is cooked and veggies are tender. | Stir, serve, and enjoy this easy hotpot hack straight from your microwave!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>68</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/87</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chili Oil Noodles</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/c6ff7a16a08e471e9aabfba49b7f9541.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Garlic 2 cloves; Ginger 1/2 tbsp; Green onions 2-3 stalks; Chili flakes 1/2 - 1 tbsp; Sesame seeds 1/2 tbsp; Sugar 1/2 tbsp; Sesame oil 1 tsp; Chinese black vinegar 1 tsp; Soy sauce 1 tbsp; MSG (optional) 1/4 tsp; neutral oil 2 tbsp; Knife cut noodles 5-6 oz</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a bowl, combine garlic, ginger, green onion, chili flakes, sesame seeds, and sugar. | Heat 2 tbsp of neutral oil (e.g., avocado oil) to 375°F, then carefully pour it over the chili flakes and aromatics. Stir well. | Add sesame oil, Chinese black vinegar, soy sauce, MSG, and salt to taste. | Cook noodles to your liking, mix them with the sauce, and add a bit of noodle water if needed to adjust the consistency. Enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>65</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/88</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Sweet and Sour Pork</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/5a5ceb9e46434edaa568357683c226c6.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>45</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Pork shoulder butt 1/2 lbs; Red bell pepper 1 piece; Yellow bell pepper 1 piece; Green bell pepper 1 piece; Red onion 1 piece; Pineapple 1/4 cup; Corn oil1-2 cups; Garlic salt 1 tsp; Soy sauce 1 tbsp; Egg 1 piece; Flour 2 tbsp; Cornstarch 4 tbsp; Ketchup 3 tbsp; Brown sugar 3 tbsp; Vinegar 2 tbsp; Salt 1/4 tsp; Water 2 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cut the pork into 1/4 to 1/2 inch pieces, slicing both parallel and perpendicular to the grain. Mix with garlic salt and soy sauce, massaging for 1 minute. Crack and beat the egg, mix with the pork for 30 seconds. Let the pork marinate while preparing the other ingredients. | Cut bell peppers, red onions, and pineapple into bite-sized pieces. | Make the sauce by mixing ketchup, brown sugar, vinegar, cornstarch, salt, and water until smooth. | Coat the pork with flour, massaging for 1-2 minutes. Add cornstarch to a plate and coat the pork pieces. | Heat oil in a wok to 300-350°F (149-176°C). Fry the pork for 7-8 minutes until browned. For a second fry, heat the oil to 400°F (204°C) and fry for 1-2 minutes. When the pork has cooked, drain on paper towel and set aside. | Stir-fry the vegetables for 30 seconds, then add the pineapple and cook for another 30 seconds. Remove from the wok. Reduce the sauce in the wok for 1-2 minutes. | Add everything back into the wok, toss with the sauce for 1-2 minutes. Serve immediately for crunchiness!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>51</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/89</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Mala Hot Pot</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/6c54942eaa53455ab8af7b58b80c74ed.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Water 4-6 cups; Mala Hot Pot Sauce (LKK SOUP BASE SC STYLE HOT &amp;amp; SPICY (MALA) 1 pack; Garlic 2 cloves; Green Onion 2-4 stalks; Soy Sauce (LKK) 2-4 tbsp; Ramen Noodles (WU-MU RAMEN NOODLE ORIGINAL) 1 pack; Canned Straw Mushrooms (ASN/TAS STRAW MUSHROOM BROKEN) 1 can; Fish Tofu (J/JANE FZ FISH TOFU) 1 cup; Milkfish Ball (J/JANE FZ MILKFISH BALL) 1 cup; Canned Baby Corn (Yifa) 1 can; Quail Eggs (ASN/TAS) 1 can; Regular Corn 1 pieces; Leafy Greens 1/2 cup; Napa Cabbage 1/2 cup; Carrots 1/2 piece; Mushrooms 1/4 cup; Croissant Ring Roll (EVERBEST CROISSANT RING ROLL) 3 pieces; Chili Sauce (AGV) 2 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a large pot add the garlic, chopped green onion, water, hot pot seasoning, and soy sauce. Stir it well and bring it to a low boil. | When the mixture has begun to boil add the noodles, canned straw mushrooms, fish tofu, fish balls, baby corn, quail eggs, corn, leafy greens, cabbage, carrot slices, fresh mushrooms, and croissant ring rolls. | Cover the pot with a lid and prepare the dipping sauce. In a small dish add about 2 tablespoons of chili sauce and set aside for later. | When the ingredients have cooked to your liking, turn off the heat. Dip your food into the chili sauce and enjoy your Mala Hot Pot!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>24</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/90</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Longevity Noodles</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/4e9f14da8fa8402680204d7cfbec73dd.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Yi Mein noodles 1/2 lbs; Cooking oil 2 tbsp; Garlic 3-4 cloves; Onion 1 piece; Carrot 1 piece; Shitake mushrooms 4-5 pieces; Chicken broth 1 cup; Oyster sauce 2 tbsp; Light soy sauce 1 tbsp; Dark soy sauce 1/2 tbsp; Sugar 1/2 tsp; Ground white pepper 1/2 tsp; Salt 1/4 tsp; Green onions 4-5 stalks; Sesame oil 1 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Boil plenty of water and cook the noodles until al dente. Drain and set aside. | Heat a wok until very hot, then add oil and swirl to coat the surface. Add garlic and onion, cooking until fragrant. Stir in carrots and mushrooms, and cook for 1 minute. | Pour in the stock, followed by oyster sauce, soy sauces, sugar, and white pepper. Bring to a boil and taste. Adjust salt if needed. | Add the noodles to the wok, gently tossing to coat with the liquid. Simmer on low heat until most of the liquid is absorbed. | Stir in the chives and sesame oil, tossing until the chives wilt. Serve immediately and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>69</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/91</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chimei Mantou</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/1ca9bab4beac44b8b6f4fa7509ee155a.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>CHIMEI FZ WHOLE WHEAT ALMOND MANTOU 5PC 1 pack; Hoisin sauce 4-6 tbsp; Roasted beef shank 1 lbs; Pickled cucumbers 1 cup; Cilantro 1 bunch; CHIMEI FZ BROWN SUGAR SLICE ROLL 6PC 1 pack; Sweetened condensed milk 1 can</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Place frozen mantou onto steamer and steam for 8-10 minutes, or until cooked. | Place the Chimei Brown Sugar Slice Rolls on a plate, and serve with one can of sweetened condensed milk for dipping. | Slice the Chimei Whole Wheat Almond Mantou in half after steaming. | Open the mantou, and spread hoisin sauce on each side. Then fill with roasted beef shank, pickled cucumbers, and cilantro. | Serve and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>10</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/92</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Synear Rice Balls</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/52da22efcbd546398dff001de574c42b.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Water 4-6 cups; Rock sugar 3-4 pieces; SYNEAR RICE BALL PURPLE CHESTNUT 1 pack; SYNEAR AUTHENTIC RICE BALL SESAME 1 pack; SYNEAR MINI RICE BALL SESAME/PEANUT/STRW 1 pack</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a large saucepan add water and rock sugar, then bring to a low boil until the rock sugar has dissolved. | After the rock sugar has dissovled in the water, add in the frozen Synear Tan Yuan to the saucepan. | Boil the Synear Tan Yuan for about 4 minutes. | Seve the Tan Yuan in a bowl with the rock sugar water and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>9</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/93</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Buddha&apos;s Delight (Lo Hon Zai)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/f2a126aaad18494cb96e26b265df0652.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>60</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Dried shitake mushroom 3-4 pieces; Dried lily flower 1/4 cup; Wood ear fungus (or black fungus) 1/8 cup; Mung bean vermicelli 1/2 oz; Bean curd sheet 1 sheet; Cabbage 1/2 cup; Bamboo shoots 1/4 cup; Carrot 1 piece; Baby sweet corn 1/4 cup; Fatt choy (black moss) 2 tsp; Sugar 2 tbsp; White fermented bean curd 1/2 cup</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Tie knots in lily flowers, then cut the carrots, bamboo shoots, mushrooms and cabbage. | Soak dry ingredients (lily flowers, wood ear fungus, shiitake mushrooms, black moss) until soft. Reserve mushroom water. | Cut the bean curd sheet into smaller pieces, deep-fry for 15-20 seconds, then drain. | Heat 2 tablespoons of vegetable oil in a wok and stir-fry the cabbage until slightly softened. | Add shiitake mushrooms, lily flowers, wood ear fungus, black moss, carrots, fermented bean curd, sugar, mushroom soaking water, and extra water. Braise for 2 minutes. | Break the fried bean curd into smaller pieces and lay them on top. | Place mung bean vermicelli over the bean curd, cover, and braise for 5 minutes until soft, adding water if needed. | Add bamboo shoots and baby sweet corn. Continue braising until the vegetables are tender and the sauce thickens. | Mix everything well and serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>16</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/94</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese Peanut Cookies</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/74d46fd408274091a68c951c0a73d4ab.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>60</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Creamy peanut butter 3/4 cups; Peanut oil 3 tbsp; Flour 1 3/4 cups; Powdered sugar 4/7 cups; Salt 1/4 tsp; Egg 1 piece; Water 1 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a large mixing bowl, combine peanut butter, sugar, flour, and salt. Use a wooden spoon to stir until evenly mixed. Gradually add half of the cooking oil, mixing as you go rather than pouring it all in at once. Continue adding the remaining oil slowly, incorporating it with your hands until a cohesive dough forms. If the dough feels too dry, add more oil, one teaspoon at a time, until it holds together without crumbling. | Roll the dough into 1-tablespoon-sized balls and arrange them on a parchment-lined cookie sheet, spacing them about 1/4 inch apart. | Use a fork to gently flatten the dough ball while creating a crisscross pattern, or simply press a half piece of peanut on top of the cookie dough. | Prepare the egg wash by whisking together one beaten egg and one teaspoon of water. Lightly brush the cookies with the egg wash, then bake at 350°F on the middle rack for 15–18 minutes. Rotate the pan halfway through baking to ensure even browning. The cookies should turn golden brown. If making larger cookies, extend the baking time by a few minutes as needed. | Remove from the oven and let them rest for about 15 minutes before transferring them to a cookie rack to cool completely. Once fully cooled, serve and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>38</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/95</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Dua Mon (Vietnamese Pickled Daikon)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/679b10ee68964cc78d2258fff50d7941.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>180</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Daikon 1 piece (about 2 lbs); Sea salt 1 tbsp; Fish sauce 1/2 cup; Brown sugar 1/2 cup (packed); Water 1/4 cup; Garlic 2-3 pieces; Red chili pepper 1-2 pieces</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cut the daikon into 4-inch pieces, then slice each piece into small wedges. Place the cut daikon in a large mixing bowl, add salt, and toss to combine. Let the mixture sit for 2 hours to allow the water to pool at the bottom. Afterward, rinse the daikon and squeeze out the excess salt in batches. | Arrange the daikon on a wire rack set over a baking sheet and preheat the oven to its lowest setting, usually around 170°F. Allow it to dry for 1-2 hours, or longer if necessary. | In a small saucepan, combine the fish sauce, brown sugar, and water. Heat the mixture over medium heat until it begins to bubble, then remove from the heat. Allow it to cool to room temperature. | Transfer the dried daikon to a jar with a lid and add the sliced garlic and chili peppers. | Pour the brine into the jar and secure with a lid. Let it sit at room temperature for 24 hours, then transfer it to the fridge. It will be ready to eat after 1 day, but the flavor will improve with time. When stored in the fridge, it can last for up to 8 months.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>17</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/96</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Tteokguk (Korean Rice Cake  Soup)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/87e2161155064c67acdcf7d921a74c37.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>45</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Sliced rice cakes (tteok) 1 lbs; Water 5-7 cups; Beef stew meat (or flank steak/brisket) 1/2 lbs; Garlic 2-4 cloves; Green onion 2-3 stalks; Vegetable oil 3 tsp; Eggs 2 pieces; Fish sauce 1 tbsp; Sesame oil 1 tsp; Black pepper 1/2 tsp; Toasted seaweed paper (nori) 1 sheet; Red pepper 1 piece; Salt 2 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Start preparing the ingredients by cutting the beef, garlic, green onions, and red pepper. Then separate the egg yolks from whites, and season with salt. | In a medium pan, cook the egg yolks then slice into strips. | While the burner is on roast the seaweed paper sheet (nori) and set aside. | In a large pot begin boiling about 5-7 cups of water at medium heat. When the water is at a rapid boil add in the garlic, beef, sliced rice cakes (tteok), fish sauce, and salt. | Add in the egg whites to the soup and continue to stir while pouring to create ribbons of egg whites. Then add  sesame oil, black pepper, and green onions. | Remove from heat and serve the rice cake soup into bowls. Garnish with yellow egg strips, crushed seaweed, red pepper and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>14</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/97</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Soy Braised Tilapia</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/b0827730d4b34cccb8c5dd021d582371.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Tilapia (filets) 1 lbs; Vegetable oil 1 tsp; Ginger 1 tbsp; Garlic 1 tbsp; Light sodium soy sauce 1/4 cup; Rice vinegar 1/4 cup; Green onions 1/4 cup; Cilantro 1/4 cup; Crushed chili 1/2 tsp; Water 1/4 cup</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat oil in a deep skillet over medium heat. Add ginger and garlic, sautéing for 30 to 60 seconds until fragrant. | Place the fish fillets on the hot oil and fry for about 1 minute. Then add soy sauce, water, scallions, cilantro, crushed chili, and vinegar to the skillet. Bring everything to a boil, then cover and let it cook for 3-4 minutes. | Once done, remove from heat and transfer to a plate, drizzling the flavorful sauce over the fish. Garnish with extra green onions and cilantro. Enjoy over white rice!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>24</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/98</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Garlic Shrimp Pasta</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/7915fcab36e845b69933274849c73cd2.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>99 Ranch Organic Brown Rice Pasta 1 pack; Vegetable oil 1 tbsp &amp;amp; 1/4 cup; Peeled and deveined shrimps 1 lbs; Garlic 3-4 cloves; 99 Ranch chilli flakes 1 tsp; 99 Ranch soy sauce 2 tbsp; Oyster sauce 2 tbsp; Green onions 3 stalks; Ginger 1 piece; Salt 1 tsp; Sesame oil 2 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Use a mortar and pestle to mash the spring onion, ginger, and salt into a rough paste. Next heat vegetable oil and sesame oil in a small saucepan over medium-high heat and pour it over the spring onion mixture. Stir and set aside. | Cook the pasta in salted boiling water until al dente. Make sure to save 1 cup of pasta water. | Heat 1 tablespoon of vegetable oil in a pan over medium heat. Add garlic, shrimp, and chili flakes. Cook for 2-3 minutes until the shrimp turn pink. Stir in soy sauce and oyster sauce, simmer briefly, then turn off the heat. | Drain pasta and add it to the pan. Turn heat to high and toss for 2-3 minutes until the sauce thickens. Add pasta water if needed. | Stir in the spring onion sauce, mix well, and serve!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>41</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/99</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Lee Kum Kee Kimchi Fried Rice</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/d571cfbe3d2b432892c50d92bbfee500.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Cooking oil 1 tbsp; Chopped onion 2 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Minced Garlic 1 tbsp; Cooked rice 1 bowl; Kimchi (cut to pieces) 1 cup; Eggs 2 pieces; Chopped green onions 1 tbsp; Shredded seaweed as desired; Cooked white sesame 1 tsp; Lee Kum Kee Panda Brand Oyster Flavored Sauce 2 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Premium Pure Sesame Oil 1 tbsp; Kimchi juice 1/3 cup</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a heated wok, add cooking oil and sauté the chopped onion and minced garlic until it is a little charred. Add in cooked rice and mix well (need to press down to break the rice clump). Then add in kimchi and kimchi juice to stir fry. | Add in seasoning and stir fry well before serving in a plate. | In addition, crack the eggs in to boiling water and cook slowly for 3 minutes to make poached eggs. | Finally, sprinkle with chopped green onion, shredded seaweed and cooked white sesame to complete. | Tips: adding oyster sauce to this dish can help boost the flavor.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>29</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/100</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Braised Korean Short Ribs (Galbijjim)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/04365f93bcda484a9e0202384689c20f.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>75</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Beef short ribs 4-5 lbs; Yellow onion 1 piece; Ginger 5-6 slices; Garlic 5-6 cloves; Turnips (can use daikon or Chinese radish) 8 pieces; Shimeji mushrooms (or Shitake mushrooms) 1 pack; Carrots 3 pieces; HANASIA KOREAN BBQ SAUCE KALBI 1 bottle; Water 8 cups &amp;amp; 4 cups; Dried jujubes (optional) 2-3 pieces</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Boil the beef short ribs in 8 cups of water for 10 minutes, then drain and rinse to clean the meat. | Transfer the cleaned short ribs to a large pot and add 1 bottle of Hanasia Korean BBQ sauce (kalbi) along with 4 cups of water, ensuring the meat is fully submerged. Bring to a boil over medium heat and cook for 30-45 minutes, or longer for more tender ribs. | Meanwhile, peel and slice the onion, garlic, ginger, turnips, mushrooms, and carrots. Add all the vegetables except the onions to the pot, cover, and simmer for 20 minutes. | Uncover, then add the onions and optional dried jujubes. Cook for another 10 minutes, or until the sauce thickens. | Serve over white rice and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>79</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/101</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Korean Gimbap</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/69990fd3770a4516abc3c44220fd823c.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>35</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Seaweed paper 5 sheets; Cooked rice 4 cups; Beef skirt steak (or tenderloin, or ground beef) 1/2 lbs; Carrot 1-2 pieces; Yellow pickled radish 4-5 pieces; Spinach 1 bunch; Eggs 2-3 pieces; Garlic 3 cloves; Soy sauce 2 tsp; Sugar 1 tbsp &amp;amp; 1 tsp; Salt 1 tsp; Sesame oil 2 tbsp; Vegetable oil (to cook the egg) 1 tsp; Black pepper 1 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Place freshly cooked rice in a large, shallow bowl. Gently mix in salt and sesame oil using a rice scoop or wooden spoon. Set aside. | Blanch spinach, then mix in minced garlic, salt, and sesame oil in a bowl. | Cut carrot into matchsticks, mix with salt, and let it sit for 5-10 minutes. Heat a pan with a few drops of vegetable oil. Squeeze out excess water from the carrot, then sauté for 1 minute. Place next to the spinach. | Trim fat from skirt steaks and slice into ¼ inch wide strips. Mix with soy sauce, minced garlic, black pepper, 1 tablespoon + 1 teaspoon brown sugar, and sesame oil. | Heat a pan over medium-high and cook the marinated beef, stirring until fully cooked. Set aside. | Beat 3 eggs with ¼ teaspoon salt. Heat a 10-12 inch non-stick pan with a few drops of oil. Wipe off excess oil with a paper towel, leaving a thin layer. Pour egg mixture into the pan, spreading it into a large circle. | Once the bottom is cooked, flip the egg and remove from heat. Let it cook in the pan for 5 minutes without browning. Slice into ½ inch strips and set aside with spinach. | To roll the gimbap, place a sheet of gim on a bamboo mat with the shiny side down. Spread about ¾ cup of rice, leaving 2 inches uncovered at the top. | Add beef, carrot, pickled radish, egg strips, and spinach in the center. Roll the mat tightly, pressing as you go. | Brush with sesame oil and sprinkle with sesame seeds. Slice into ¼ inch pieces with a sharp knife, wiping the knife clean between cuts. Serve and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>52</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/102</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Sesame Soba Noodles</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/dd9229b6d0a84aaf90540972212a8a49.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Soy sauce 1/4 cup; Sesame oil 3 tbsp; Rice vinegar 2 tbsp; Brown sugar 1 tbsp; Ginger 1 tsp; Black pepper 1 tsp; Soba noodles (buckwheat noodles) 1 pack; Vegetable oil 1 tbsp; Green onion 3 stalks; Sesame seeds 2 tbsp; Seaweed flakes 1/2 cup</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a mixing bowl, combine the soy sauce, sesame oil, vinegar, brown sugar, ginger, and pepper. Stir well and set aside. | Cook the buckwheat noodles according to the package instructions. | Once cooked, rinse them under cold running water until fully cooled. Drain thoroughly and set aside. | Heat oil in a wok or skillet over medium heat. Add half of the green onions and sauté for about 30 seconds. | Pour in the prepared sauce and bring to a boil. Let it simmer and thicken slightly, about 15 seconds. | Add the noodles and the remaining green onions to the pan. Toss everything together until evenly coated. | Add in sesame seeds and crumbled seaweed flakes, then mix well. | Garnish with more green onion, sesame seeds, crumbled seaweed flakes and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>41</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/103</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Lee Kum Kee Boiled Seafood Platter</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/2c855e6c6eef4b749d59d2f2d0ca1233.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Shell-on shrimp 10 oz; Mussels 8 pieces; Squid rings 6 oz; Crab sticks 4 pieces; Fresh scallops 6 oz; Vegetable oil 4 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Minced Garlic 3 tbsp; Minced millet pepper 2 tbsp; Chopped scallion (for garnish) 2 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Liquid Seasoning 6 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Pure Sesame Oil 1 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cook the seafood in separate batches in boiling water, draining each well and placing onto a plate. | Heat the oil in a pot and quickly stir-fry the Lee Kum Kee Minced Garlic and millet pepper until fragrant. | Drizzle the mixture over the cooked seafood. | Scatter chopped scallion over the dish, and drizzle the seafood with Lee Kum Kee Liquid Seasoning and Lee Kum Kee Pure Sesame Oil to serve.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>5</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/104</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Japanese Beef Curry</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/2dc94e88ac0e4d3fb8aecde6c155da84.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>40</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Vegetable oil 1 tsp; Cubed beef (can use chuck roast or stew meat) 1/2-1 lbs; Onion 1 piece; Carrot 1-2 pieces; Potato 1 piece; Garlic 2 cloves; Water 2 cups; Japanese curry cube 1 cube</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat oil in a pot over medium heat and sear beef for 2 minutes until browned, then remove and set aside. | Add onions and garlic then cook for about 8 minutes until soft and caramelized. | Stir in cut carrots and potatoes, and cook for 1 more minute. | Return beef to the pot and add 2 cups of water. | Stir, cover, and simmer for 20 minutes, stirring occasionally. | Stir in Japanese curry roux cube until fully dissolved, then bring back to medium-low heat and simmer for another 15 minutes until thickened. | Enjoy over rice!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>55</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/105</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese Tea Eggs</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/26a368ba619241e18821d58d15c3535a.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>60</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Eggs 1 dozen; Light soy sauce 4 tbsp; Dark soy sauce 2 tbsp; Bay leaves 2-3 pieces; Sichuan peppercorns 1 tsp; Star anise 1-2 pieces; Cinnamon stick 1 piece; Sugar 2 tsp; Salt 1 tsp; Black tea 2 tea bags; Water 3 cups</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Mix all marinade ingredients in a small pot. Bring to a boil, then lower the heat and simmer for 10 minutes. Let it cool completely, then remove the tea bags. | Boil enough water to cover your eggs. Lower the heat and gently add the eggs using a spoon. (Soft-boiled: 5 minutes, Medium: 7 minutes, or Hard-boiled: 10 minutes) | Transfer eggs to a bowl of ice water for 2–3 minutes, or rinse with cold tap water until cool. Then gently crack the shells with a spoon (don’t break the eggs), or peel them if you prefer. | Transfer the eggs to a container, then pour in the marinade along with the dry ingredients and marinate overnight for peeled eggs, or 24 hours for cracked “marble” eggs. | Peel the eggs and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>23</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/106</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chicken Satay</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/a736abefd5e44b6aa854c5ac7a3f0c3b.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>60</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Bonless chicken thighs 1 lbs; Coconut milk 1 can; Curry powder 1 tbsp; Sugar 1 tsp + 1/4 cup; Red curry paste 2 tsp + 2 tbsp; Salt 1 tsp + 1 tsp; Apple cider vinegar 2 tbsp; Dark soy sauce 2 tsp; Peanut butter 1/2 cup; Water 1/2 cup; Crushed peanuts 1 tbsp; Lime 2 pieces; Cilantro 1 bunch; Thai chili 2 pieces; Bamboo skewers 1 pack</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Make the marinade by mixing together 1 tbsp curry powder, 1 tsp sugar, 2 tsp red curry paste, and 1 tsp salt. | Now mix the chicken pieces with the marinade and ¼ cup coconut milk. Let sit for at least 20 minutes or overnight. | Place about 4–5 chicken pieces onto each skewer. | Heat oil in a large non-stick pan over medium-high and cook skewers in batches, about 3 minutes per side until golden. | In a saucepan, combine remaining coconut milk with 2 tbsp red curry paste, 1/2 cup peanut butter, 1/4 cup sugar, 2 tsp dark soy sauce, 1 tsp salt, 2 tbsp cider vinegar, and 1/2 cup water. | Stir and simmer over medium-low heat for 5 minutes, stirring occasionally. | Pour some sauce into a bowl and sprinkle with crushed peanuts. Pile satay skewers onto a platter, sprinkle with remaining peanuts, coriander and chilli. | Serve with sauce on the side for dipping and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>42</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/107</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Hawaiian Loco Moco</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/6a3a3623739946cfa05305a193b79489.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>40</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Eggs 1-2 pieces; Unsalted butter 2 tbsp; Onion 1 piece; Mushrooms (sliced) 1 pack; Cooked rice 2 cups; Green onions 3 stalks; Ground beef 1 1/2 lbs; Worcestershire sauce 1 tbsp + 1 tsp; Seasoning salt 1 tsp; Garlic powder 1 tsp; Black pepper 1/2 tsp; Beef stock 1 1/2 cup; Soy sauce 4 tsp; Ketchup 2 tsp; Cornstarch 5 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a large bowl, mix ground beef, Worcestershire sauce, seasoning salt, garlic powder, and black pepper. Shape into thick, round patties (about 1 inch thick), smoothing the edges. | Heat a pan over medium heat and cook patties for 3–5 minutes on each side, or until fully cooked. Set cooked patties on a paper towel-lined plate to drain excess grease. | In the same pan, melt 1 tbsp butter and sauté onions for 1 minute, then add mushrooms for another 1–2 minutes. | Whisk together beef stock, shoyu, Worcestershire sauce, ketchup, and cornstarch until smooth. Stir until it thickens and starts to simmer. | Melt a little butter in a pan, crack in the egg, and cook sunny-side up (or to your preference). Set aside. | Scoop hot rice onto a plate, add a hamburger patty, pour over the gravy, and top with the egg. | Garnish with green onions and serve hot!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>47</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/108</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Salmon Fillet with Mushroom</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/115b9670ecd54e6da31110070fa2964b.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>White Mushrooms 250g; Salmon Fillet 2 pieces; Asparagus Spears 4-6 pieces; Onion (chopped) 20g; Lee Kum Kee Minced Garlic 10g; Lee Kum Kee Supreme Authentic First Draw Soy Sauce 2 tbsp; Lee Kum Kee Coarse Ground Black Peppercorns A pinch; Water 3 tbsp; Sugar 1 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Sauté Lee Kum Kee Minced Garlic and chopped onions until fragrant. Add Lee Kum Kee Supreme Authentic First Draw Soy Sauce, water, and sugar. Bring to a boil and mix well. Remove from heat and set the sauce aside. | Blanch the asparagus until tender, then drain and arrange on a serving plate. | Heat oil in a pan over medium heat. Pan-fry the white mushrooms until golden brown. Add 2 tablespoons of the prepared sauce, stir well, and remove from the pan. | Heat oil in the pan again and add the salmon fillets. Sprinkle with Lee Kum Kee Coarse Ground Black Peppercorns and cook over low heat until fully cooked. Remove from the pan and place on the serving plate. | Drizzle the remaining sauce over the salmon fillets and serve immediately. | Tips: To prevent the salmon fillets from sticking to the pan, sprinkle a small amount of salt onto the heated pan before adding the salmon.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>15</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/109</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Mango Lassi</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/c0a12a7a652b46a5b30bdbddc5426441.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>10</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Fresh mango 1 piece; Milk 1/2 cup; Plain yogurt 1/3 cup; Mango puree 1/3 cup; Ice cubes 6-8 pieces; Sugar 2 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Add mango, milk, yogurt, mango pulp, cane sugar (start with less add more if needed), and ice to a high-speed blender. Blend on high until smooth. | Taste and adjust: add more sugar for sweetness, more pulp for mango flavor, or a bit more yogurt for tang. | Serve right away and enjoy! Or refrigerate, covered, for up to 24 hours.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>47</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/110</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Egg Skin Dumplings (Dan Jiao)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/82830ef94f7b44a49a8ace492346fa4b.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>50</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Green onion 3 stalks; Garlic 1 clove; Ginger 1 tsp; Ground pork 1/2 lbs; Soy sauce 1 tbsp + 1 tsp; Sesame oil 1/2 tsp + 1 tsp; Rice wine vinegar 1/2 tsp + 1/2 tsp; Ground black pepper 1/2 tsp; Chili flakes 1/2 tsp; Tapioca starch (or potato starch) 1/2 tsp + 1/2 tsp; Eggs 4-5 pieces; Water 1 tbsp; Chicken bullion 1 tsp; Black sesame seeds 1 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a bowl, combine pork mince, spring onion, garlic, ginger, soy sauce, sesame oil, rice wine vinegar, black pepper, chili flakes, and starch. Mix with a fork or chopsticks until it becomes a paste, then set aside. | Whisk together eggs, water, and potato starch until smooth. | Heat a lightly oiled ladle over medium heat. Pour in a spoonful of the egg mixture and spread it into a circle. When the bottom is set and the top is still slightly wet, add a spoonful of pork filling to the center. Fold the egg over into a half-moon shape and gently press the edges with a spatula to seal. Set aside and repeat until all the mixture is used. | In a steamer carefully add the dumplings, cover, and simmer for 8 minutes. | Make the dipping sauce. In a pan, add water, chicken stock cube, soy sauce, sesame oil, and rice wine vinegar. Stir and bring to a simmer. | Plate the dumplings, spoon over the sauce, and top with spring onion, chili, and black sesame seeds. Enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>19</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/111</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese BBQ Cumin Lamb Skewers</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/b40953c401fc4a3b9d9a580d3650eb41.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>35</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Red chili flakes 1 tbsp; Cumin 1 tbsp; Fennel 2 tsp; Coarse salt 1 tsp; Garlic powder 2 tsp; Boneless lamb shoulder 2 lbs; Canola oil 1 tbsp; Shaoxing wine 2 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Grind chili flakes, cumin, and fennel. Add garlic and salt, then briefly grind to mix. Set aside 1 tablespoon of the spice mix. | Cut boneless lamb shoulder into 1-inch pieces. | Toss lamb with the rest of the mix, oil, and Shaoxing wine. | Thread the lamb tightly onto skewers, leaving a 3-inch handle and the tip exposed. | Grill skewers over medium high heat for about 4–6 minutes per side, until cooked through. | Remove from grill and sprinkle the extra spice mix over the skewers, then serve! | Tip: Soak bamboo skewers in cold water for at least 2 hours or overnight.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>20</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/112</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Indomie Spring Rolls</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/95ee51b5a10640be8c5d90130d3fd86d.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Indomie Mi Goreng BBQ Chicken Flavor 1 pack; Rice paper wrapper 1 pack; Cucumber strips (remove seeds) 1 piece; Cilantro 1 bunch; Turkey Spam 1 can; Sweet Chili Sauce for dipping</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Boil the Indomie noodles for 3 minutes, drain, and mix with seasoning packets. | Prepare the fillings. Wash and cut the cucumber. Rise the cilantro. Slice and pan-fry the Turkey Spam until golden. | Soften the rice paper. Fill a shallow dish with warm water. Dip a rice paper sheet for 5-10 seconds until just soft. (don&amp;#x27;t over-soak) Lay it flat on a clean surface. | Assemble the rolls. In the center of the rice paper, layer a piece of Turkey Spam, a few cucumber strips, cilantro, and Indomie noodles. Fold in the sides, then roll tightly from the bottom like a burrito. Serve with a side of sweet chili sauce.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>15</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/113</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Cambodian Black Pepper Beef</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/40245a23b89e4c29a3a626fa9ae8c3be.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>45</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Steak (cut into 1½ inch pieces) 1 lbs; Vegetable oil 1 tbsp; Red onion 1 piece; Tomato 1 piece; Lettuce 1 bunch; Steamed rice 1-2 cups; Oyster sauce 1 tbsp + 2 tbsp; Soy sauce 1 tbsp + 1 tbsp; Dark soy sauce 2 tsp; Black pepper 1 tsp + 1 tsp; Cornstarch 1 tsp; Baking soda 1/2 tsp; Garlic 1-3 cloves; Sugar 1 tsp; Lime juice 1 tsp; Salt 1 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a medium bowl, combine 1 tablespoon oyster sauce, 1 tablespoon soy sauce, 2 teaspoons sweet dark soy sauce, 1 teaspoon ground Kampot pepper, 1 teaspoon cornflour (cornstarch), ½ teaspoon baking soda, and 2 finely grated garlic cloves. Mix well until the cornflour and baking soda are fully dissolved and the marinade is smooth and evenly blended. | To make the stir-fry sauce, mix together 2 tablespoons oyster sauce, 1 tablespoon soy sauce, and 1 teaspoon sugar. Stir until the sugar is fully dissolved and the sauce is smooth and well combined. Set aside for later. | In a small bowl, combine 3 tablespoons lime juice, 1 teaspoon ground Kampot pepper, and 1 teaspoon sea salt. Stir well until the salt is mostly dissolved. Set aside until ready to serve. | Heat vegetable oil in a wok or large pan over high heat. Add beef in a single layer and sear for 30 seconds, then toss. Repeat 3 times until lightly charred. Add onions and toss briefly, then pour in the stir-fry sauce. Toss for 30 seconds (or longer for well-done). Turn off heat and let rest in the pan for 1 minute. | Arrange lettuce on a serving plate, top with tomato slices and beef. Serve with steamed rice and dipping sauce.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>15</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/114</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Indonesian Fried Rice (Nasi Goreng)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/73e23d19c2f242b4b80a652a026f0f81.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>25</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Chicken breast 1/2 lbs; Vegetable oil 1 1/2 tbsp; Kecap manis (sweet soy sauce) 1 tbsp + 2 tbsp; Garlic 2-3 cloves; Red chili 1 piece; Onion 1 piece; Cooked white rice 3-4 cups; Shrimp paste 2 tsp; Eggs 4 pieces; Green onion 2 stalks; Tomato 1 piece; Cucumber 1 piece; Fried shallots for garnish; Lime wedge 1-2 pieces</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Heat oil in a large pan or wok over high heat. | Add the chili and garlic, stirring for about 10 seconds until fragrant, then add the onion and sauté for 1 minute. | Next add the chicken and cook until it starts to turn white. Stir in 1 tablespoon of kecap manis and continue cooking for another minute, or until the chicken is nearly cooked through and lightly caramelized. | Add the cooked white rice, 2 tablespoons of kecap manis, and shrimp paste (if using). Stir continuously for about 2 minutes, until the sauce thickens and the rice begins to caramelize—this step is essential for flavor! | Garnish with green onions, red chili, fried shallots, and fried eggs. Serve with lime wedges, tomato, and cucumber, then enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>15</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/115</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Taiwanese Popcorn Chicken</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/31837f92b1ed4f17a3e45f7c2987870c.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>45</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Chicken thighs 1 lbs; Soy sauce 2 tbsp; Ginger (minced) 1 tbsp; Garlic (minced) 1 tbsp; White pepper powder 1/2 tsp + 1/2 tsp; Shaoxing wine 1/2 tbsp; Egg whites 1 egg; Sweet potato flour 2 cups; Five spice powder 1/2 tsp; Salt 1/2 tsp; Sugar 1/2 tsp; Basil 1 bunch; Vegetable oil 2 cups</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cut 1 lb of chicken thighs into uniform 2-inch pieces. | Marinate with soy sauce, grated ginger, grated garlic, white pepper, Shaoxing wine, and egg white. Mix well and refrigerate for at least 30 minutes, or up to 24 hours. | In a small bowl, combine five spice powder, white pepper, salt, and sugar to make the seasoning; set aside. | Coat the marinated chicken evenly in sweet potato flour, ensuring no spots are left bare. | Fry at 350°F for 3–4 minutes, then add fresh basil and cook for an additional 30 seconds. | Sprinkle with the seasoning immediately after frying, and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>24</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/116</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Taiwanese Dan Bing (Egg Pancake)</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/0ea3be35e5eb4b60ae893c8b5ae94bee.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>35</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>All purpose flour 1/2 cup; Water 2/3 cup; Salt 1/4 tsp; Green onion 1 bunch; Egg 3-4 pieces; Vegetable oil 1 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>In a medium bowl mix together the flour, water, and salt until smooth with no lumps. The batter should be very thin consistency. Set the batter aside and let the mixture rest for 30 minutes. | Next, prepare the filling ingredients. Start by thinly slicing the green onions, then beat the eggs in a small mixing bowl, and set both aside. | Warm a large non-stick pan on medium heat and lightly brush with vegetable oil. | Pour 1/4 cup of the batter on to the pan and swirl around until the bottom on the pan is evenly coated. Cook for about 2 minutes then flip and cook the other side making sure that the pancake is lightly browned. Remove and set aside. | Then pour in the beaten egg and swirl the pan until there is an even layer of egg. While the egg is still wet generously sprinkle green onion and place the pancake on top. Make sure to press the pancake into the egg so that it sticks together and cook for another minute. | When the egg is fully cooked flip it and carefully roll the pancake so that the egg is on the inside. | Slice into bite sized pieces and serve with soy sauce!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>16</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/117</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese Boiled Peanuts</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/31371a0af7c54c2ba5d340d6a74db752.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>75</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Raw peanuts (in shell) 1 1/2 lbs; Water 8 cups; Sea salt 1 tbsp; Sichuan peppercorns 1 tbsp; Cinnamon sticks 1-2 sticks; Bay leaves 3 leaves; Star anise 2-3 pods</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Soak the peanuts in water for about 30 minutes to loosen any dirt on the shells. Wash them thoroughly and drain. Repeat if needed until the water runs clear. | Using your thumb and index finger, gently press and crack open the pointier end of each peanut. This allows the brine to penetrate the shells more effectively. | Place the peanuts in a medium pot and add 8 cups of water, ensuring they are fully submerged. Stir in 1 tablespoon of sea salt (adjust to taste), 1 tablespoon Sichuan peppercorns, 1-2  cinnamon sticks, 3 bay leaves, and 2-3 star anise pods (use 2 for a milder flavor or 3 for stronger). | Bring the pot to a boil, then cover, reduce the heat, and simmer for 45 minutes to 1 hour. This will yield slightly firm peanuts. For softer peanuts, extend the cooking time and taste periodically to reach your desired texture. | Turn off the heat and leave the pot covered so the peanuts continue to absorb the briny flavors. Allow them to cool to room temperature. For best results, let the peanuts soak overnight in the refrigerator and enjoy them cold.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>4</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/118</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Stir Fry Lotus Root</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/97a46d462bb2411585c121d1ebc1568f.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Lotus Root 2 pieces; Black fungus (or wood ear mushrooms) 8-10 pieces; Red bell pepper 1 piece; Chicken stock 1/4 cup; Oyster sauce 2 tsp; Salt 1/2 tsp; Sugar 1/4 tsp; White pepper 1/4 tsp; Vegetable oil 2 tbsp; Ginger 1 piece; Garlic 3 cloves; Green onions 3 stalks; Shaoxing wine 1 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Peel and trim 2 pieces of lotus root, then thinly slice them. Soak and prepare 8–10 pieces of black fungus (or wood ear mushrooms), and slice 1 red bell pepper into thin strips. Mince 3 cloves of garlic, slice 3 stalks of green onions, and thinly slice 1 piece of ginger. | Bring a large wok or pot of water to a boil. Add the lotus root, black fungus, and bell pepper, and blanch for 45 seconds. Drain thoroughly and set aside. | In a small bowl, combine 1/4 cup chicken stock, 2 tsp oyster sauce, 1/2 tsp salt, 1/4 tsp sugar, and 1/4 tsp white pepper. Stir well and set aside. | Heat 2 tbsp vegetable oil in the wok over medium heat. Add the sliced ginger and cook for 30 seconds to 1 minute until fragrant. Add the minced garlic and green onions, and cook for another 20 seconds. | Add the blanched lotus root, black fungus, and bell pepper to the wok. Stir-fry for 1 minute, then pour 1 tbsp Shaoxing wine around the perimeter of the wok. | Mix the stir fry sauce well then add it to the wok. Stir-fry for another 20–30 seconds, until the sauce thickens and coats the vegetables evenly. | Transfer to a serving plate and enjoy while hot!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>29</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/119</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese Chicken &amp; Mushroom Soup</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/fa0a4dcddc2c4e63aedc405c0aa7419c.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>120</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Dried shitake mushroom 1 1/2 cups; Water 8 cups; Dried goji berry 2 tbsp; Dried red Chinese dates 6 pieces; Whole chicken (cut into pieces) 3 lbs; Vegetable oil 1 tbsp; Ginger (sliced) 1 piece; Shaoxing wine 3 tbsp; Salt 2 tsp; Green onion 4 stalks</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Wash 1½ cups of dried shiitake mushrooms a couple of times and rinse thoroughly. Soak them in 8 cups of water in a soup pot for at least 3 hours or overnight. After soaking, cut the stems and return the mushrooms to the pot of soaking water. | Add 2 tablespoons of dried goji berries and 6 pieces of dried red Chinese dates to the soup pot (no need to soak these beforehand). Bring the mixture to a boil over high heat, then immediately lower the heat to a simmer. | While the soup is simmering, wash 1 whole chicken (about 3 lbs) and pat it dry with a paper towel. Trim and set aside the chicken breasts for another dish. Cut the remaining parts of the chicken into large pieces and set aside. | After the soup has simmered for about 30 minutes, heat a wok over medium-high heat until it just begins to smoke. Reduce the heat to medium, then add 1 tablespoon of vegetable oil and 1 piece of sliced ginger. Cook for 1–2 minutes until fragrant. Swirl the oil to coat the wok, then spread the chicken pieces in a single layer. Lightly brown them on all sides, stirring occasionally, until most pieces are cooked through. Turn off the heat. | Add the browned chicken to the soup pot. Deglaze the wok with ½ cup of water, then pour the liquid into the soup pot as well. Add 3 tablespoons of Shaoxing wine, cover, and simmer over medium heat for another 30 minutes. | Season the soup with 2 teaspoons of salt, adjusting to taste. Garnish with 4 stalks of chopped green onion right before serving.</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>14</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/120</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese Pumpkin Rice Cake</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/23bf0f3a9a5d4465a869dae366dac3af.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Pumpkin 2 cups; Sugar 3 tbsp; Glutinous rice flour 3 cups; Vegetable oil 2 tbsp; Sesame seeds 1 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Steam a small pumpkin, and scoop out the flesh from the skin into a large mixing bowl. | Next add in the glutinous rice flour and sugar to the bowl, then mix well with your hands until a stiff dough begins to form. | Take about two tablespoons of the dough and flatten it out into a small pancake shape. | In a large nonstick pan add vegetable oil and turn the burner to medium low heat. Then carefully add in the pumpkin rice cakes and cook each side until golden brown. (about 2 minutes per side) | After the rice cakes have turned golden brown remove from the pan and serve with sesame seeds for garnish. | Let cool before serving, and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>7</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/121</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chinese Sausage Stuffing</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/582c65f7cc6b41b990c6a9f97c1488dd.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>60</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>French bread 1 loaf; Chinese sausage 3-4 pieces; Butter 1 stick; Brown onion 1 piece; Shallot 3 pieces; Celery 4 stalks; Garlic 3 cloves; Parsley 3 tbsp; Thyme 1 tbsp; Salt 1 tsp; Soy sauce 1 tbsp; Sesame oil 2 tsp; Chicken stock 2 cups; Egg 1 piece</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cut the bread into cubes and toast in the oven at 350F for 25 minutes or until golden brown. | While the bread is in the oven prepare the other ingredients. Slice the Chinese sausage, onion, shallots, celery, garlic, parsely, and thyme. | Heat a large pan on medium and cook down the Chinese sausage until the oil renders out. Then remove the Chinese sausage from the pan. | Using the same pan melt the butter and sautee the vegetables until everything has softened. | Season the mixture with salt, soy sauce, and sesame oil. | Next, add in the parsely, thyme, and Chinese sausage. Stir the mixture well and add 1 cup of chicken stock. Let mixture simmer for 5 minutes so that some of the chicken stock reduces. | Place the toasted bread cubes into a large bowl and add the mixture. | In a separate bowl mix together chicken stock and an egg, then pour over the stuffing mixture. | Pour the stuffing mixture into a greased baking dish and bake at 350F for 1 hour. | Remove from the oven and garnish with more parsley and thyme before serving, and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>4</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/122</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Sichuan Hot Pot Soup Stock</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/67611c56ca474c95999e7015327cce73.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>90</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Sichuan peppercorns 1/3 cup +  1 tsp for garnish; Dried chili peppers 1/2 cup + 8-10 pieces for garnish; Cinnamon sticks 2 sticks; Bay leaves 4 leaves; Star anise 2 pods; Cumin seeds 1 tsp; Fennel seeds 1 tsp; Cloves 1/2 tsp; Neutral cooking oil 3 cups; Garlic 6 cloves; Ginger 1 tsp; Green onions 5 stalks; Doubanjiang (Spicy Fermented Bean Paste) 1/2 cup; Fermented black beans (can use paste or sauce) 3 tbsp; White sugar 1 tsp; Shaoxing wine 1 tbsp; Chicken bouillon 3 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Blend the dried chili peppers, sichuan peppercorns, cumin seeds, cloves, fennel seeds, star anise, bay leaves, and cinnamon sticks until they’re small flakes (not a powder). | Heat oil over low heat until gently hot (a tiny piece of garlic should sizzle softly). Add garlic, ginger, and green onion. Cook for about 2 minutes until fragrant, not browned. | Stir in the doubanjiang and fermented black beans. Cook for 1 minute. | Add the blended spices. Cook for about 10 minutes, stirring often, until the oil turns a bright orange-red. | Add sugar, Shaoxing wine, and Chicken bouillon. Stir to dissolve. | Remove from heat and let the mixture cool for 10–20 minutes. | Pour into a heatproof container. Top with whole dried chilis and crushed peppercorns. Cover and freeze overnight. | Once frozen, cut into 4 pieces. Store each piece in a zip-top bag in the freezer for up to 6 months. One piece = one small hot pot (or one side of a divided pot). | **To use the hot pot stock, add it to 4-5 cups of water (or chicken broth). Heat and stir to dissolve the soup base, then you’re ready to cook when it&amp;#x27;s boiling!**</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>5</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/123</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Strawberry Santa Tanghulu</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/937562c2d8664eea96c122e876d23a46.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Strawberries 1 pack; Bananas 2 fruits; White sugar 2 cups; Water 1 cup; Black sesame seeds 1/4 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cut off about ⅓ of the strawberry—this pointed piece will be Santa&amp;#x27;s hat. | Layer the skewer with the strawberry base, a slice of banana, then top with the strawberry &amp;quot;hat.&amp;quot; Add black sesame seeds for Santa&amp;#x27;s eyes. | In a small pot, combine sugar and water over medium heat, stirring until the sugar fully dissolves. Once dissolved, stop stirring and let it simmer for 10–15 minutes until the syrup turns golden brown. Watch closely so it doesn&amp;#x27;t burn. | To check if it&amp;#x27;s ready, dip a wooden chopstick into the syrup, then into ice water for 3 seconds. If it hardens and crunches when bitten, it&amp;#x27;s ready. | Turn off the heat. Dip the assembled fruit into the syrup, then immediately into ice water. Place on a plate and let it set—within 3 minutes, the sugar will harden and won&amp;#x27;t stick. | Once the sugar has hardened and cooled completely, it&amp;#x27;s ready to eat!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>5</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/124</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>5-Spice Peking Chicken</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/eb3e23c5cc1f41049b62a55733670219.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>180</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Whole chicken 2-3 lbs; Five-spice powder 1/2 tsp + 1 tsp; Light soy sauce 1/4 cup; Dark soy sauce 2 tbs; White sugar 1 tbs; Ginger 6 slices; Honey 1 tbs</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Lightly dust the inside of the chicken with ½ tsp of five-spice powder. | Make the marinade by mixing together ¼ cup light soy sauce, 2 tablespoons dark soy sauce, 1 tablespoon sugar, 5-6 slices ginger, and 1 teaspoon five-spice powder. | In a large bowl or Ziploc bag, combine the marinade and coat the chicken. Marinate for at least 4 hours, preferably overnight. | Remove the chicken from the fridge 30 minutes before cooking and stuff it with the ginger from the marinade. | Place the chicken on a tray with a rack (or crumpled foil balls if you don’t have a rack) for proper airflow. | Pour the leftover marinade into a small pot and simmer on low for 5–10 minutes. | Stir in 2 tbsp of maple syrup or honey to sweeten and thicken. Set aside for basting. | Preheat the oven to 350°F (177°C). | Place the chicken in the oven. After 20 minutes, you’ll see oil drippings—use them to baste every 20 minutes for an hour. If no drippings, brush 1–2 tbsp of oil instead. | After an hour, switch to basting with the prepared sauce every 10–15 minutes until it’s used up (about 30 minutes). | Remove the chicken when it reaches 165°F (74°C), roughly 1.5 hours (depending on size). Let it rest 10–15 minutes before slicing. | Once cool, serve and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>8</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/125</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Jellyfish Salad</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/e66d726906c948dc9004169e23b68474.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>15</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Instant Jellyfish 1 packet; Salt 2 tsp; White sesame seeds 2 tbsp; Vegetable oil 3 tbsp; Garlic 2 cloves; Green onion 3 stalks; Red pepper flakes 1 tsp; Rice vinegar 3 tbsp; Soy sauce 1 tbsp; Sesame oil 2 tsp; Sugar 1 1/2 tsp; White pepper 1/2 tsp; Chinese celery 5-6 stalks</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Rinse the jellyfish under cold water. Toss it with 2 teaspoons of salt in a bowl, then transfer to a strainer set over the bowl. Let it drain for 10 minutes to remove excess water. | In a skillet, heat neutral oil and pour over the red pepper flakes, garlic, and scallion whites. Cook until fragrant and softened, about 1 minute. | In a bowl, mix the rice vinegar, soy sauce, sesame oil, sugar, and white pepper until the sugar dissolves. Add the drained jellyfish and celery, then stir in the garlic oil until well combined. Cover and refrigerate for at least 1 hour. | Just before serving, toss the jellyfish with 1 tablespoon of the toasted sesame seeds. Top with scallion greens, celery leaves, and the remaining sesame seeds. Enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>1</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/126</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Gyudon with HonDashi</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/cb2f411622744d9ab51fd5fe1c69b56b.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Thinly sliced beef 1/2 lbs; Yellow onion (sliced) 1/2 cup; Green onions 3-4 stalks; Ginger (minced) 1 tsp; Shoyu 1 tbsp; Shaoxing wine 1 tbsp; Mirin 1 tbsp; Sugar 1/2 tsp; HonDashi 1 tsp; Water 1/2 cup</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Prepare the vegetables. Thinly slice the onions, green onions, and ginger then set aside. | Heat a large pan over medium-high heat. Then add water, HonDashi powder, shaoxing wine, sugar, mirin, and soy sauce. Cover the lid and bring the sauce to boil. | Once the sauce is boiling, add the sliced onions, and ginger. | When the onion is tender, add in the thinly sliced beef and cook until no longer red. | Serve the meat and sauce over steamed rice. Top with extra green onion and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>6</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/127</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Chicken Mei Fun</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/41ffc71342684cf4bdc1488f1885791d.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>35</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Thin rice vermicelli noodles 8 oz; Vegetable oil 2 tbsp + 3 tbsp; Dark soy sauce 1/2 tsp; Chicken breast (strips) 1/2 lbs; Cornstarch 1 tsp; Water 1 tbsp + 2 tbsp; Oyster sauce 2 tsp; Shaoxing wine 2 tsp; White pepper 1/4 tsp + 1/4 tsp; Five spice powder 1/8 tsp; Ginger 3 slices; Shallots (sliced)  4 pieces; Carrot (shredded) 1 piece; Cabbage (shredded) 1 cup; Green onion 4 stalks; Light soy sauce 1 1/2 tbsp; Sesame oil 1/2 tsp; Salt 1/8 tsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Soak the dried rice noodles according to the package instructions until soft (they should no longer feel hard when you bite one). Drain well and shake off any excess water. | In a large bowl, toss the noodles with 1 teaspoon oil and ½ teaspoon dark soy sauce. Set aside. | In a medium bowl, combine the chicken, cornstarch, water, oyster sauce, Shaoxing wine, white pepper, five spice, and vegetable oil. Mix well and marinate for 20 minutes. | While the chicken marinates, prep the ginger, shallots, carrot, cabbage, and scallions. Have everything ready before cooking. | Heat a wok over high heat. Add 3 tablespoons oil, then add the ginger and chicken. Stir-fry until the chicken is just cooked through. Add the shallots and stir-fry for 10 seconds, then add the cabbage and carrots and cook for another 30 seconds. | Season with 1½ tablespoons light soy sauce, ½ teaspoon sesame oil, and ¼ teaspoon white pepper. Stir to combine. | Add the prepared noodles and scallions. Reduce heat to medium and stir-fry until everything is evenly mixed and heated through. Season with salt to taste then enjoy! | *** For firmer noodles, serve immediately. For softer noodles, add 2 tablespoons water, cover, and cook over low heat for 1 minute before serving.***</poc_instructions>
            <poc_likes>1</poc_likes>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/128</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Red Bean Soup</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/ce01869255e041e3b517ec463e2f2fe6.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>90</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Dried red beans (Adzuki Beans) 2 1/2 cup; Dried lotus seeds 1/3 cup; Dried lily bulb 1/3 cup; Rock sugar 1/3 cup; Brown sugar 1 3/4 cup; Dried mandarin peel 2 peels; Salt 1/2 tsp; Water 6 cups</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Rinse the red beans under clean water, then drain. Rinse once more to remove any dust, then drain again. Cover the beans with fresh water and soak for at least 1 hour or overnight. Do not soak longer than 24 hours, or they may begin to sprout. Rinse the lotus seeds and dried lily bulbs. Cover them with water and soak for at least 1 hour as well. | Add 6 cups of water, 1/2 teaspoon salt, the soaked red beans, and 2 pieces of dried mandarin peel to a large pot. Bring to a boil over high heat. Once boiling, reduce to low heat and simmer for 30 minutes. | Add the soaked lotus seeds and lily bulbs. Continue simmering on low heat for another hour. After about 1½ hours total, the beans should be soft and easy to crush between your fingers. For a softer texture, cook longer. For firmer beans, reduce the cooking time. | Add rock sugar and brown sugar. Stir until fully dissolved. Large pieces of rock sugar may take a little longer to melt. | To thicken the soup, either mash some of the beans directly in the pot or mix cornstarch and water in a 1:2 ratio until smooth, then slowly stir it into the soup. | If the soup becomes too thick, add a little water to adjust. Taste and add more sugar if needed. Serve warm, or refrigerate and enjoy cold later.</poc_instructions>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/129</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>8 Treasure Rice</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/87f875833b384e158cb34be37078e1fa.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>65</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Glutinous rice 1 1/2 cups; Coconut oil 2 tbsp; Sugar 2 tbsp; Red bean paste 3-4 tbsp; Jujubes (red dates) 3 pieces; Golden raisins 1 tbsp; Pumpkin seeds 1 tbsp; Goji berries 1/2 tbsp; Walnuts 1-2 pieces; Dried chrysanthemum buds 1 tbsp; Cornstarch 1 tsp; Water 1 cup</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Cover the glutinous rice with about 2 inches of cold water. Soak for at least 3 hours, or preferably overnight. | Drain and rinse the soaked rice a few times. Mix in the coconut oil and sugar. Stir well until the sugar melts and the rice is evenly coated. | Arrange the toppings in the bottom of a wide heat-proof bowl after coating the bowl with more coconut oil. Begin with the walnuts in the middle, then jujubes, raisins, goji berries, and pumpkin seeds. | Spoon two-thirds of the rice into the bowl over the toppings. Gently press it down without disturbing the design. Create a small dent in the center and fill it with red bean paste, spreading it into a thin layer. | Add the remaining rice on top and smooth the surface. | Return the assembled bowl to the steamer. Steam for another 60 minutes. | While the rice is steaming, combine water, sugar, and chrysanthemum buds in a small saucepan. Bring to a boil over medium heat, then reduce to medium-low and simmer for 10 minutes. | Mix cornstarch with 1 teaspoon of water until fully dissolved. Stir the slurry into the saucepan. Continue cooking and stirring until the syrup slightly thickens. Strain into a bowl and discard the chrysanthemum buds. | When the rice is finished steaming, spoon a few tablespoons of syrup over the top. Let it rest for 10 minutes. | To serve, place a plate over the bowl and carefully flip it over in one quick motion. Remove the bowl and pour the remaining syrup on top. Serve warm.</poc_instructions>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/130</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Tofu Miso Soup with HonDashi</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/04f43e95fb6d41af8a09a5cf9df8bbe4.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>20</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Extra firm tofu 1 pack; Green onion 2-3 stalks; Hon Dashi 2 tsp; Water 3 cups; Miso paste 2 tbsp</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Press the tofu to remove the excess moisture. Then cut the tofu into small cubes and slice the green onions, then set aside. | Add the tofu and green onions to a medium sized pot, then cover with water. | Next, add in the HonDashi powder and bring everything to a low boil. | Reduce the heat to low and mix in the miso paste into the soup until it is well dissolved. | Serve while hot and garnish with extra green onions. Enjoy!</poc_instructions>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

    <url>
        <loc>https://www.99ranch.com/recipe-detail/131</loc>
        <lastmod>2026-03-04</lastmod>
        <coveo:metadata>
            <title>Salmon Ochazuke with HonDashi</title>
            <content_type>Recipe</content_type>
            <image>https://img.awsprod.99ranch.com/f819880c88744772b5e5f696792e2886.jpeg</image>
            <poc_cooking_time>30</poc_cooking_time>
            <poc_ingredients>Cooked salmon 1 fillet; Cooked short grain rice 1 cup; Crispy puffed rice (bubu arare) 1 tsp; Shredded nori 1 tsp; White sesame seeds 1/2 tsp; Wasabi 1/2 tsp; Water 1 cup; Mirin 1 tsp; Soy sauce 1 tsp; Salt 1/8 tsp; Hon Dashi 2 tsp; Green tea 1 bag; Green onion 2 stalks</poc_ingredients>
            <poc_instructions>Prepare the salmon and rice. Remove the skin and bones from 1 precooked salmon fillet, then flake the salmon into bite-size pieces and set aside. Cook 1 cup of rice, following the instructions on the package. | Heat a saucepan on low. Combine water and Hon Dashi until everything dissolves, then steep 1 green tea bag for 2-3 minutes then remove. | Add 1 tsp mirin, 1 tsp soy sauce, and ⅛ tsp salt to the saucepan. Bring it to a boil and set aside. | For each serving, add 1 cup of cooked rice to a bowl. Top with flaked salmon. Sprinkle 1 teaspoon of bubu arare (or crushed rice crackers), 1 teaspoon shredded nori, ¼ teaspoon toasted white sesame seeds over the top, and 1/2 tsp wasabi. | When you‘re ready to eat, pour the hot dashi green tea mixture over the salmon and rice until it&amp;#x27;s halfway submerged. Garnish with green onions and enjoy!</poc_instructions>
        </coveo:metadata>
    </url>

</urlset>
